[{"qid": "time_0_ua_en", "question": "Valentino Lazaro played for which team from 1994 to 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1_ua_en", "question": "Which team did the player Domenico Caso belong to from 1944 to 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_2_ua_en", "question": "Marco Ferrante played for which team between 1956 and 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_3_ua_en", "question": "Federico Bonazzoli played for which team from 1998 to 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_4_ua_en", "question": "Which team did Luciano Bodini play for between 1962 and 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_5_ua_en", "question": "Which team did Mame Thiam play for between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_6_ua_en", "question": "Annibale Frossi played for which team in 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_7_ua_en", "question": "Which team did Orazio Rancati play for between 1947 and 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_8_ua_en", "question": "Which team did the player Vampeta belong to from 1966 to 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_9_ua_en", "question": "Silvio Pietroboni played for which team in the year of 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_10_ua_en", "question": "Filippo Mancini played for which team between 1997 and 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_11_ua_en", "question": "What was the position of George V in the year of 1938?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_12_ua_en", "question": "What position did Prithvi Narayan Shah take in 1777?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_13_ua_en", "question": "What position did Princess Zhejue take in 403?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_14_ua_en", "question": "What position did Po Tisuntiraidapuran take during 1795?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_15_ua_en", "question": "Which position did Wuffa of East Anglia hold in the year of 580?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_16_ua_en", "question": "What was the position of Po Tisuntiraidapuran during 1795?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_17_ua_en", "question": "Ibrahim Njoya took which position in 1935?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_18_ua_en", "question": "What was the position of Gwangjong of Goryeo in 977?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_19_ua_en", "question": "Dokka Umarov took which position during 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_20_ua_en", "question": "Alexander I of Scotland took which position in the year of 1126?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_21_ua_en", "question": "What position did Napoleon Louis Bonaparte take during 1833?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_22_ua_en", "question": "Ngawang Namgyal took which position from 1500 to 1505?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_23_ua_en", "question": "What position did Empress Matilda take in 1169?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_24_ua_en", "question": "Which position did Gongyang of Goryeo hold in the year of 1396?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_25_ua_en", "question": "Which position did Edward the Elder hold in the year of 926?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_26_ua_en", "question": "What was the position of Donyo in the year of 1514?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_27_ua_en", "question": "Which position did Chungnyeol hold during 1310?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_28_ua_en", "question": "What position did Talorgan II take during 784?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_29_ua_en", "question": "Chungnyeol took which position in the year of 1310?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_30_ua_en", "question": "Which position did Ngwane V hold in 1901?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_31_ua_en", "question": "What position did Levi Woodbury take during 1853?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_32_ua_en", "question": "Jacques Delors took which position from 1955 to 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_33_ua_en", "question": "What position did Jacques Santer take between 1953 and 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_34_ua_en", "question": "Ward Hunt took which position during 1888?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_35_ua_en", "question": "What was the position of William Paterson in the year of 1808?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_36_ua_en", "question": "What position did Willis Van Devanter take during 1943?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_37_ua_en", "question": "Which position did David Souter hold from 1980 to 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_38_ua_en", "question": "What position did Abe Fortas take in 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_39_ua_en", "question": "Which position did Thomas Campbell Clark hold in 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_40_ua_en", "question": "What was the position of Joseph Story during 1847?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_41_ua_en", "question": "Which position did Edward Douglass White hold in the year of 1923?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_42_ua_en", "question": "Which position did Romano Prodi hold between 1967 and 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_43_ua_en", "question": "Sonia Sotomayor took which position from 1974 to 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_44_ua_en", "question": "Stanley Forman Reed took which position during 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_45_ua_en", "question": "Which position did Charles Evans Hughes hold in the year of 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_46_ua_en", "question": "William Johnson took which position in 1836?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_47_ua_en", "question": "What position did Samuel Blatchford take in 1895?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_48_ua_en", "question": "Mike Rogers took which position from 1976 to 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_49_ua_en", "question": "Which position did William Henry Moody hold in 1919?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_50_ua_en", "question": "What position did Horace Gray take during 1904?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_51_ua_en", "question": "What was the position of John Hessin Clarke during 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_52_ua_en", "question": "What was the position of Sicco Mansholt in the year of 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_53_ua_en", "question": "Which position did Brett Kavanaugh hold from 1990 to 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_54_ua_en", "question": "What position did Samuel Alito take between 1970 and 1975?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_55_ua_en", "question": "Which position did Jean Rey hold in the year of 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_56_ua_en", "question": "What position did Howell Edmunds Jackson take during 1897?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_57_ua_en", "question": "What award was endowed to Flemming Lentfer in 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_58_ua_en", "question": "Which award did Hubert Lynes receive during 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_59_ua_en", "question": "Markkleeberg received which award during 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_60_ua_en", "question": "Which award did Ainring receive during 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_61_ua_en", "question": "What award was endowed to An Unbelievable Story of Rape in 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_62_ua_en", "question": "Semyon Kosberg received which award during 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_63_ua_en", "question": "Which award did Alexander III of Russia receive during 1896?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_64_ua_en", "question": "What award was endowed to Frederick II of Prussia in the year of 1788?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_65_ua_en", "question": "What award was endowed to Arthur Balfour in 1932?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_66_ua_en", "question": "Which award did Bill Pickering receive in 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_67_ua_en", "question": "Which award did Daizhan Cheng receive during 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_68_ua_en", "question": "What award was endowed to Rafael Hui in 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_69_ua_en", "question": "Which award did Graz receive during 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_70_ua_en", "question": "Athens received which award in 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_71_ua_en", "question": "Bonn Minster received which award during 1942?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_72_ua_en", "question": "Rita Moreno received which award in the year of 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_73_ua_en", "question": "Which award did Sherlock Holmes receive in 1882?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_74_ua_en", "question": "Ivan Selifonov received which award in the year of 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_75_ua_en", "question": "Henry VIII of England received which award during 1549?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_76_ua_en", "question": "Ivan Selifonov received which award in 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_77_ua_en", "question": "What award was endowed to Central Volga Krai in 1938?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_78_ua_en", "question": "What was the name of the employer Rexford Tugwell work for during 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_79_ua_en", "question": "Which employer did Patricia Harris work for from 1988 to 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_80_ua_en", "question": "Which employer did John Celivergos Zachos work for in 1900?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_81_ua_en", "question": "George Forsythe was an employee for whom during 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_82_ua_en", "question": "Which employer did Cornelius Lanczos work for during 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_83_ua_en", "question": "Who did Thomas Pynchon work for between 1945 and 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_84_ua_en", "question": "Which employer did Robert Love work for from 1999 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_85_ua_en", "question": "Which employer did Laurent Rossi work for between 1986 and 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_86_ua_en", "question": "Which employer did Tianyi Geng work for from 2004 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_87_ua_en", "question": "Manu Cornet was an employee for whom from 2000 to 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_88_ua_en", "question": "What was the name of the employer David Weinberger work for between 2012 and 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_89_ua_en", "question": "Which employer did Arnnon Geshuri work for between 1997 and 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_90_ua_en", "question": "Which employer did Jarkko Oikarinen work for between 1955 and 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_91_ua_en", "question": "Who did Quoc Viet Le work for from 1999 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_92_ua_en", "question": "What was the name of the employer Ifeoma Ozoma work for between 2004 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_93_ua_en", "question": "Which employer did Samy Bengio work for from 1972 to 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_94_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was West Yorkshire located between 1963 and 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_95_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Prince Edward Island belong to between 1866 and 1871?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_96_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was East Midlands located from 1983 to 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_97_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Cleveland belong to from 1961 to 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_98_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was preserved county of Wales located from 1989 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_99_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Humberside belong to in the year of 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_100_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Budapest located from 1981 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_101_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did West Lothian belong to from 1953 to 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_102_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Newry and Mourne District Council located between 1963 and 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_103_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Moray belong to between 1962 and 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_104_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was City of Edinburgh located between 1960 and 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_105_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Vale of Glamorgan located between 1962 and 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_106_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did County Down belong to between 1914 and 1919?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_107_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Edinburgh belong to from 1692 to 1697?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_108_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was East Lothian located between 1958 and 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_109_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Wismar belong to from 1621 to 1626?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_110_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Rhode Island belong to from 1775 to 1780?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_111_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Galicia belong to between 1922 and 1927?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_112_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Alytus District Municipality located from 1923 to 1928?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_113_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Kaunas District Municipality located between 1946 and 1951?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_114_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Kaunas District Municipality belong to between 1943 and 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_115_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Jurbarkas District Municipality located from 1896 to 1901?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_116_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Skuodas District Municipality located between 1924 and 1929?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_117_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Kalisz Voivodeship located in 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_118_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district was Ignalina District Municipality located between 1942 and 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_119_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Vilnius District Municipality belong to between 1916 and 1921?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_120_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Skuodas District Municipality belong to between 1944 and 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_121_ua_en", "question": "Which adminstrative district did Vilnius District Municipality belong to from 1935 to 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_122_ua_en", "question": "Where was Alexander Neckam educated during 1219?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_123_ua_en", "question": "Where was Pierre de Villiers educated between 1960 and 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_124_ua_en", "question": "Rodolphe Belmer went to which school between 1968 and 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_125_ua_en", "question": "Which school did Pierre Schill go to from 1969 to 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_126_ua_en", "question": "Which school did Louis Rossel go to in the year of 1873?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_127_ua_en", "question": "Arnaud de La Grange went to which school from 1973 to 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_128_ua_en", "question": "Where was Olivier de Germay educated from 1969 to 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_129_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was going on in TikTok from 2008 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_130_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to TikTok between 2008 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_131_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to Germany from 1943 to 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_132_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to NTT Docomo Yoyogi Building from 1990 to 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_133_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was going on in HMS Erebus from 1830 to 1835?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_134_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to Panathenaic Stadium from 1992 to 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_135_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was going on in Vasily Lazarev in 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_136_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to Yusaku Maezawa from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_137_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to Mark Shuttleworth between 1996 and 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_138_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to Richard Garriott from 1994 to 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_139_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was going on in Mamoru Mohri between 1993 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_140_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was going on in Mamoru Mohri from 1982 to 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_141_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was going on in Klim Shipenko from 2014 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_142_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to Dennis Tito between 1991 and 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_143_ua_en", "question": "What significant event was happening to Yulia Peresild between 2014 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_144_ua_en", "question": "Where did Caspar Schmalkalden work in the year of 1675?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_145_ua_en", "question": "Where did Konstantin Somov work in the year of 1941?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_146_ua_en", "question": "Theodor de Bry worked in  which location in the year of 1600?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_147_ua_en", "question": "Eva Zeisel worked in  which location in 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_148_ua_en", "question": "What was the working location for George Soros from 1924 to 1929?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_149_ua_en", "question": "What was the working location for Anders Zorn during 1922?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_150_ua_en", "question": "George Herriman worked in  which location in 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_151_ua_en", "question": "What was the working location for Thomas Eakins during 1918?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_152_ua_en", "question": "Where did Dominique Vivant work during 1827?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_153_ua_en", "question": "Nikolai Sheremetev worked in  which location in 1811?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_154_ua_en", "question": "What was the working location for Lee Miller in 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_155_ua_en", "question": "Where did Henry VII of England work during 1511?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_156_ua_en", "question": "Where did Josep Maria Subirachs work in 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_157_ua_en", "question": "Where did Guillaume Apollinaire work in 1920?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_158_ua_en", "question": "What was the working location for Paolo Troubetzkoy in 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_159_ua_en", "question": "Who owned PZL Mielec from 1928 to 1933?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_160_ua_en", "question": "Who owned Ainola from 1962 to 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_161_ua_en", "question": "Who owned The Great Masturbator between 1984 and 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_162_ua_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Mount Vernon between 1741 and 1746?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_163_ua_en", "question": "Who owned Saint George between 1846 and 1851?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_164_ua_en", "question": "The Tempest was owned by whom between 1841 and 1846?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_165_ua_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Hotel Bellevue Palace from 1950 to 1955?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_166_ua_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Palais Wilson between 1902 and 1907?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_167_ua_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Bank of England from 1931 to 1936?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_168_ua_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Dante and Virgil in Hell between 1995 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_169_ua_en", "question": "Who owned The Magpie from 1976 to 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_170_ua_en", "question": "Palau became a member of what organization or association during 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_171_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Yemen join in 1916?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_172_ua_en", "question": "Turkmenistan became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_173_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Pakistan join in the year of 1939?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_174_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Kiribati join in the year of 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_175_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Afghanistan join in 1908?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_176_ua_en", "question": "Philippines became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1898?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_177_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Tuvalu join in the year of 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_178_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Ecuador join during 1874?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_179_ua_en", "question": "Honduras became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1815?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_180_ua_en", "question": "Bolivia became a member of what organization or association in 1866?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_181_ua_en", "question": "Colombia became a member of what organization or association during 1875?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_182_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Indonesia join during 1819?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_183_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Nauru join during 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_184_ua_en", "question": "What organization did The Gambia join in 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_185_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Singapore join during 1953?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_186_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Grenada join in the year of 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_187_ua_en", "question": "What organization did East Timor join during 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_188_ua_en", "question": "Belize became a member of what organization or association during 1921?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_189_ua_en", "question": "Senegal became a member of what organization or association during 1954?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_190_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Cyprus join in 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_191_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Commonwealth of the Philippines join in the year of 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_192_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Republic of Ireland join during 1898?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_193_ua_en", "question": "Albania became a member of what organization or association during 1908?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_194_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Czech Republic join in the year of 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_195_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Kingdom of Burundi join in 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_196_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Monaco join during 1883?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_197_ua_en", "question": "What organization did United States of America join during 1855?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_198_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Turkey join in 1852?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_199_ua_en", "question": "Uzbekistan became a member of what organization or association during 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_200_ua_en", "question": "Australia became a member of what organization or association during 1864?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_201_ua_en", "question": "Iraq became a member of what organization or association in 1912?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_202_ua_en", "question": "Guatemala became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1865?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_203_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Dominican Republic join during 1819?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_204_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Ethiopia join in 1878?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_205_ua_en", "question": "Iceland became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1887?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_206_ua_en", "question": "What organization did North Macedonia join in the year of 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_207_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Ukraine join in the year of 1932?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_208_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Bahrain join in 1959?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_209_ua_en", "question": "What organization did United Arab Emirates join in the year of 1928?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_210_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Kenya join in the year of 1954?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_211_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Angola join in 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_212_ua_en", "question": "Sierra Leone became a member of what organization or association in 1951?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_213_ua_en", "question": "Mali became a member of what organization or association during 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_214_ua_en", "question": "Vanuatu became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_215_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Sudan join in 1941?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_216_ua_en", "question": "Republic of China became a member of what organization or association during 1951?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_217_ua_en", "question": "Laos became a member of what organization or association in 1936?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_218_ua_en", "question": "Israel became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1936?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_219_ua_en", "question": "Russia became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1841?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_220_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Latvia join during 1890?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_221_ua_en", "question": "Croatia became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_222_ua_en", "question": "Slovakia became a member of what organization or association during 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_223_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Tajikistan join in the year of 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_224_ua_en", "question": "Chile became a member of what organization or association during 1873?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_225_ua_en", "question": "Federation of Malaya became a member of what organization or association in 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_226_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Thailand join in the year of 1859?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_227_ua_en", "question": "Cuba became a member of what organization or association during 1851?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_228_ua_en", "question": "Germany became a member of what organization or association during 1847?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_229_ua_en", "question": "Malta became a member of what organization or association during 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_230_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Montenegro join in the year of 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_231_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Portugal join in 1853?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_232_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Central African Empire join in the year of 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_233_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Indonesia join in 1857?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_234_ua_en", "question": "United Arab Republic became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_235_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Belgium join in the year of 1858?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_236_ua_en", "question": "Brazil became a member of what organization or association during 1859?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_237_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Central African Republic join during 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_238_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Mauritius join in 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_239_ua_en", "question": "Uganda became a member of what organization or association during 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_240_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Algeria join in the year of 1881?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_241_ua_en", "question": "Guyana became a member of what organization or association in 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_242_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Fiji join in the year of 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_243_ua_en", "question": "What organization did South Africa join during 1890?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_244_ua_en", "question": "Guinea became a member of what organization or association in 1951?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_245_ua_en", "question": "Central African Republic became a member of what organization or association in 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_246_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Rwanda join during 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_247_ua_en", "question": "Papua New Guinea became a member of what organization or association in 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_248_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Tunisia join in the year of 1882?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_249_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Commonwealth realm of Guyana join in 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_250_ua_en", "question": "Nigeria became a member of what organization or association during 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_251_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Niger join in 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_252_ua_en", "question": "What organization did Antigua and Barbuda join in 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_253_ua_en", "question": "Federated States of Micronesia became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_254_ua_en", "question": "New Zealand became a member of what organization or association in the year of 1852?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_255_ua_en", "question": "What organization did India join in the year of 1852?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_256_ua_en", "question": "Venezuela became a member of what organization or association in 1867?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_257_ua_en", "question": "Republic of Ireland became a member of what organization or association during 1913?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_258_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of European Union from 1950 to 1955?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_259_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of European Union between 1941 and 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_260_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Organization of Turkic States between 2008 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_261_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Schengen Area from 1986 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_262_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Council of Europe between 1927 and 1932?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_263_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of NATO from 1914 to 1919?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_264_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Schengen Area between 1975 and 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_265_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of NATO between 1939 and 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_266_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Council of Europe between 1940 and 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_267_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Allies of the First World War during 1920?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_268_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Community of Portuguese Language Countries from 1987 to 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_269_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Commonwealth of Independent States from 1979 to 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_270_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Collective Security Treaty Organization from 1983 to 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_271_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Eurasian Customs Union from 1999 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_272_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Eurasian Economic Union from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_273_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Commonwealth of Independent States from 1980 to 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_274_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Stabilisation and Association Agreement from 1997 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_275_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Alliance for Open Media from 2001 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_276_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of British Windward Islands in 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_277_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries between 1959 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_278_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of ASEAN between 1959 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_279_ua_en", "question": "What or Who was part of Organization of Turkic States between 2010 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_280_ua_en", "question": "Which country did Annapolis Royal belong to between 1856 and 1861?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_281_ua_en", "question": "Which country did BritBox belong to between 2004 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_282_ua_en", "question": "Which country did Vision Eternel belong to from 1992 to 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_283_ua_en", "question": "Which country did Eurocorps belong to between 1967 and 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_284_ua_en", "question": "Which country did Urup belong to from 1847 to 1852?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_285_ua_en", "question": "Which country did Broutona belong to between 1845 and 1850?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_286_ua_en", "question": "Which country did Kurilsk belong to from 1717 to 1722?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_287_ua_en", "question": "Which country did Simushir belong to from 1838 to 1843?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_288_ua_en", "question": "Which country did Kunashir Island belong to between 1840 and 1845?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_289_ua_en", "question": "Which country did Sakhalin belong to from 1857 to 1862?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_290_ua_en", "question": "Which ethical group did Balthazar belong to between 1388 and 1393?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_291_ua_en", "question": "Which political party did Ilya Ponomarev belong to from 1977 to 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_292_ua_en", "question": "Which party was Jerzy Buzek a member of between 1967 and 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_293_ua_en", "question": "Which party was Oleksandr Vilkul a member of from 1996 to 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_294_ua_en", "question": "Which political party did Viktor Yanukovych belong to from 1994 to 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_295_ua_en", "question": "Which party was Konstantin Pavlov a member of between 1991 and 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_296_ua_en", "question": "Which political party did Anatoliy Fedorchuk belong to in the year of 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_297_ua_en", "question": "Which party was Valentin Demidov a member of between 1992 and 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_298_ua_en", "question": "Which party was Olga Kovitidi a member of from 1996 to 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_299_ua_en", "question": "Which party was Yuriy Boyko a member of from 1995 to 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_300_ua_en", "question": "Which party was Wilhelm Kopf a member of during 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_301_ua_en", "question": "Which party was Hans Weisbach a member of in the year of 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_302_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Seoul between 1978 and 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_303_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Australia between 1875 and 1880?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_304_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Benin between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_305_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Hong Kong from 1971 to 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_306_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Austria between 1934 and 1939?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_307_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Sofia between 1942 and 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_308_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of United States of America from 1780 to 1785?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_309_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Australia from 1892 to 1897?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_310_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of First Hatta Cabinet in 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_311_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Taipei from 1963 to 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_312_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Taipei from 1969 to 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_313_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Kyiv from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_314_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Montana between 2005 and 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_315_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Andorra from 2005 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_316_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Helsinki from 1981 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_317_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Wales from 1993 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_318_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Russia from 1983 to 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_319_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Czech Republic between 1985 and 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_320_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Taipei City Government from 1971 to 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_321_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Czech Republic from 1985 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_322_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Taipei City Government between 1976 and 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_323_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Russia from 1984 to 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_324_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of United States of America from 1768 to 1773?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_325_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Odesa Oblast from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_326_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic during 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_327_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Poland from 1957 to 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_328_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Germany between 1918 and 1923?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_329_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Canada between 1998 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_330_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of India between 1940 and 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_331_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Dominion of India during 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_332_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Germany between 1940 and 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_333_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of United Kingdom between 2002 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_334_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Russian Soviet Federative Socialist Republic in 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_335_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of India from 1938 to 1943?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_336_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Poland from 1967 to 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_337_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Italy between 1936 and 1941?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_338_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Russian Socialist Federative Soviet Republic in the year of 1924?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_339_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Italy from 1916 to 1921?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_340_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Berlin from 1930 to 1935?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_341_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Second Merkel cabinet in 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_342_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Third Cabinet of Donald Tusk between 2014 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_343_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Paris between 1971 and 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_344_ua_en", "question": "Who was in charge of Turkey between 1987 and 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_345_ua_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Lara Fabian between 1984 and 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_346_ua_en", "question": "What citizenship did Kenny Omega hold between 1973 and 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_347_ua_en", "question": "What citizenship did Dennis Kwok hold from 1968 to 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_348_ua_en", "question": "What citizenship did Alex Trebek hold in the year of 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_349_ua_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Shenae Grimes between 1978 and 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_350_ua_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Victor Li between 1936 and 1941?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_351_ua_en", "question": "What citizenship did Alvin Yeung hold from 1966 to 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_352_ua_en", "question": "What citizenship did Rafael Bienvenido Cruz hold between 1923 and 1928?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_353_ua_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Nellie Chin Yu from 1963 to 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_354_ua_en", "question": "What citizenship did Liu Qikun hold between 1977 and 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_355_ua_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Evgeny Bareev between 2000 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_356_ua_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Tom Green between 1963 and 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_357_ua_en", "question": "What citizenship did Aliocha Schneider hold from 1986 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_358_ua_en", "question": "What citizenship did Anastasia Lin hold from 1978 to 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_359_ua_en", "question": "What citizenship did Ted Cruz hold between 1956 and 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_360_ua_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Patty Tsai from 1978 to 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_361_ua_en", "question": "What citizenship did Eddie Peng hold from 1927 to 1932?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_362_ua_en", "question": "What citizenship did Jasmin Glaesser hold between 2003 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_363_ua_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Richard Lee Armstrong in the year of 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_364_ua_en", "question": "What citizenship did Frank Stallone hold in 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_365_ua_en", "question": "What citizenship did Li Hak Kan hold in the year of 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_366_ua_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Mike Schreiner between 1993 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_367_ua_en", "question": "What was the nationality of Lauren Holly from 1997 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_368_ua_en", "question": "What citizenship did Nina Dobrev hold between 1975 and 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_369_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Air Liquide from 1996 to 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_370_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Free Democratic Party between 1934 and 1939?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_371_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Social Democratic Party of Germany between 1933 and 1938?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_372_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of German Bundestag from 1923 to 1928?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_373_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Federal Ministry of Justice between 1940 and 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_374_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Free Software Foundation from 1970 to 1975?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_375_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of European Film Academy between 1979 and 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_376_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Christian Democratic Union between 1943 and 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_377_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of European Bank for Reconstruction and Development from 1969 to 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_378_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Federal Ministry of Finance between 1929 and 1934?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_379_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of La France Insoumise group from 2004 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_380_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Federal Ministry for Economic Cooperation and Development from 1946 to 1951?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_381_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of National Rally from 1962 to 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_382_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of United Russia from 1977 to 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_383_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of British Science Association from 1957 to 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_384_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Democratic Convergence of Catalonia in the year of 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_385_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Federal Ministry of Defence of Germany between 1932 and 1937?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_386_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Chinese Communist Party from 1930 to 1935?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_387_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Free Democratic Party between 1929 and 1934?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_388_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of FDP Bundestag fraction from 1942 to 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_389_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Federal Foreign Office from 1916 to 1921?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_390_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Law and Justice from 1992 to 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_391_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of United States Department of State from 1954 to 1959?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_392_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Olympique Lyonnais between 1973 and 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_393_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Wikimedia Foundation between 1976 and 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_394_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Federal Chancellery between 1934 and 1939?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_395_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Social Democratic Party of Germany between 1928 and 1933?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_396_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Cabinet of Joe Biden from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_397_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Economic Community of West African States from 1949 to 1954?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_398_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Max Planck Society between 1931 and 1936?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_399_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Federal Foreign Office from 1944 to 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_400_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of UEFA from 1945 to 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_401_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of RUSADA from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_402_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Convergence and Union in the year of 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_403_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Christian Democratic Union from 1935 to 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_404_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Federal Ministry for Economic Affairs and Climate Action between 1937 and 1942?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_405_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of SPD Berlin between 1923 and 1928?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_406_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Social Democrats from 1955 to 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_407_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of CDU Berlin between 1935 and 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_408_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology from 1968 to 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_409_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Independent Republicans in the year of 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_410_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of World Athletics from 1898 to 1903?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_411_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Russian Social Democratic Labour Party during 1919?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_412_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Union for a Popular Movement during 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_413_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Committee on Foreign Affairs from 1940 to 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_414_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Canadian Alliance in 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_415_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Bank of Italy from 1871 to 1876?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_416_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of World Athletics from 1905 to 1910?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_417_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Conservative Party of Canada between 1983 and 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_418_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of International Olympic Committee between 1878 and 1883?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_419_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Union for a Popular Movement during 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_420_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of The Republicans from 2005 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_421_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of International Olympic Committee from 1885 to 1890?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_422_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chair of Office of the High Commissioner for Human Rights from 1977 to 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_423_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of European Movement International between 1925 and 1930?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_424_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head of Wikimedia Foundation from 1997 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_425_ua_en", "question": "European Atomic Energy Community was a part of what between 1953 and 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_426_ua_en", "question": "Finland was a part of what between 1984 and 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_427_ua_en", "question": "Romania was a part of what between 1993 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_428_ua_en", "question": "European Coal and Steel Community was a part of what during 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_429_ua_en", "question": "Poland was a part of what between 1989 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_430_ua_en", "question": "United Kingdom was a part of what between 1962 and 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_431_ua_en", "question": "Sylhet Region was a part of what from 1847 to 1852?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_432_ua_en", "question": "Pierrefonds was a part of what between 1987 and 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_433_ua_en", "question": "Sylhet Region was a part of what between 1836 and 1841?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_434_ua_en", "question": "Gabu was a part of what from 1966 to 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_435_ua_en", "question": "Golm was a part of what between 1993 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_436_ua_en", "question": "Klein Glienicke was a part of what between 1928 and 1933?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_437_ua_en", "question": "High Speed Photometer was a part of what from 1976 to 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_438_ua_en", "question": "Cosmic Origins Spectrograph was a part of what between 2001 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_439_ua_en", "question": "Faint Object Camera was a part of what from 1977 to 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_440_ua_en", "question": "Wide Field and Planetary Camera was a part of what from 1979 to 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_441_ua_en", "question": "Corrective Optics Space Telescope Axial Replacement was a part of what between 1987 and 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_442_ua_en", "question": "Space Telescope Imaging Spectrograph was a part of what from 1984 to 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_443_ua_en", "question": "Goddard High Resolution Spectrograph was a part of what from 1981 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_444_ua_en", "question": "Faint Object Spectrograph was a part of what from 1978 to 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_445_ua_en", "question": "Advanced Camera for Surveys was a part of what between 1994 and 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_446_ua_en", "question": "Maine was a part of what between 1640 and 1645?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_447_ua_en", "question": "European Union Civil Service Tribunal was a part of what in 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_448_ua_en", "question": "Where did Thomas Romain live between 1990 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_449_ua_en", "question": "What was the residence of Michael Redmond from 1968 to 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_450_ua_en", "question": "Where did Christabel Pankhurst live during 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_451_ua_en", "question": "Where did Ferenc Rofusz live from 1926 to 1931?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_452_ua_en", "question": "What was the residence of Rahaf Mohammed from 2011 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_453_ua_en", "question": "What was the residence of Wolf Koenig in 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_454_ua_en", "question": "Where did Alexandre Alexeieff live in the year of 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_455_ua_en", "question": "Where did Maurice Ascalon live in the year of 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_456_ua_en", "question": "Where did Ferenc Rofusz live between 1932 and 1937?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_457_ua_en", "question": "What operated Orbiter Processing Facility between 1972 and 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_458_ua_en", "question": "What was the operator of astronaut transfer van from 2011 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_459_ua_en", "question": "What operated Embassy of Turkey in Austria from 1906 to 1911?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_460_ua_en", "question": "What operated reCAPTCHA between 2002 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_461_ua_en", "question": "What was the operator of Wikipedia between 1992 and 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_462_ua_en", "question": "What operated Fort Barry between 1901 and 1906?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_463_ua_en", "question": "What operated Fort Washington Park from 1794 to 1799?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_464_ua_en", "question": "What was the operator of Fort Tilden between 1902 and 1907?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_465_ua_en", "question": "What was the operator of Molli railway between 1867 and 1872?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_466_ua_en", "question": "What was the operator of Anfield between 1876 and 1881?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_467_ua_en", "question": "What operated Brooks Air Force Base during 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_468_ua_en", "question": "What was the operator of MOD St Athan in the year of 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_469_ua_en", "question": "What was the operator of Robert Schumann Hochschule from 1959 to 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_470_ua_en", "question": "What was the operator of USS Foote from 1912 to 1917?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_471_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Saint Petersburg between 1943 and 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_472_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Amman from 1977 to 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_473_ua_en", "question": "Bordeaux was twinned with which city from 1905 to 1910?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_474_ua_en", "question": "Salzburg was twinned with which city between 1947 and 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_475_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Miami Beach between 1952 and 1957?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_476_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Delhi between 1995 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_477_ua_en", "question": "Nagoya was twinned with which city between 1945 and 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_478_ua_en", "question": "Berlin was twinned with which city from 1957 to 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_479_ua_en", "question": "New York City was twinned with which city between 1945 and 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_480_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Tbilisi from 1961 to 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_481_ua_en", "question": "Beijing was twinned with which city from 1959 to 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_482_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Taipei between 1954 and 1959?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_483_ua_en", "question": "Amman was twinned with which city from 1963 to 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_484_ua_en", "question": "Zagreb was twinned with which city from 1951 to 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_485_ua_en", "question": "Tokyo was twinned with which city between 1946 and 1951?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_486_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Moscow between 1930 and 1935?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_487_ua_en", "question": "New York City was twinned with which city from 1937 to 1942?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_488_ua_en", "question": "Auckland was twinned with which city from 1958 to 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_489_ua_en", "question": "Mexico City was twinned with which city between 1959 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_490_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Berlin between 1954 and 1959?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_491_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of San Francisco between 1947 and 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_492_ua_en", "question": "Lusaka was twinned with which city between 1957 and 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_493_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Yerevan from 1951 to 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_494_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Cotonou from 1955 to 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_495_ua_en", "question": "Rio de Janeiro was twinned with which city from 1947 to 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_496_ua_en", "question": "Vinnytsia was twinned with which city between 1985 and 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_497_ua_en", "question": "Los Angeles was twinned with which city from 1931 to 1936?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_498_ua_en", "question": "Eilat was twinned with which city between 1945 and 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_499_ua_en", "question": "Shanghai was twinned with which city from 1963 to 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_500_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Kunming from 1970 to 1975?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_501_ua_en", "question": "Tehran was twinned with which city from 1965 to 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_502_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Shanghai between 1940 and 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_503_ua_en", "question": "City of Brussels was twinned with which city from 1980 to 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_504_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Aalborg Municipality between 1922 and 1927?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_505_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Tokyo between 1930 and 1935?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_506_ua_en", "question": "Leiria was twinned with which city between 1955 and 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_507_ua_en", "question": "Milan was twinned with which city from 1951 to 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_508_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Buenos Aires between 1955 and 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_509_ua_en", "question": "Beijing was twinned with which city between 1964 and 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_510_ua_en", "question": "Erfurt was twinned with which city from 1957 to 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_511_ua_en", "question": "Montevideo was twinned with which city between 1989 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_512_ua_en", "question": "Tbilisi was twinned with which city from 1956 to 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_513_ua_en", "question": "Santiago was twinned with which city from 1983 to 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_514_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Riga between 1933 and 1938?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_515_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Huaibei between 2011 and 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_516_ua_en", "question": "Havana was twinned with which city from 1941 to 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_517_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Kyoto Prefecture between 1974 and 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_518_ua_en", "question": "Milan was twinned with which city between 1954 and 1959?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_519_ua_en", "question": "Luanda was twinned with which city from 1981 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_520_ua_en", "question": "La Paz was twinned with which city between 1963 and 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_521_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Bamako from 1955 to 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_522_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Damascus from 1989 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_523_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Yerevan between 1949 and 1954?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_524_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Toyama Prefecture from 1978 to 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_525_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Saint Petersburg from 1943 to 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_526_ua_en", "question": "Salzburg was twinned with which city from 1955 to 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_527_ua_en", "question": "Toronto was twinned with which city between 1961 and 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_528_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Duisburg from 1935 to 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_529_ua_en", "question": "Oslo was twinned with which city from 1978 to 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_530_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Santiago de Compostela between 1988 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_531_ua_en", "question": "Macau was twinned with which city from 1925 to 1930?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_532_ua_en", "question": "Tokushima Prefecture was twinned with which city from 1973 to 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_533_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Chicago between 1937 and 1942?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_534_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Madison between 1955 and 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_535_ua_en", "question": "Osaka was twinned with which city between 1942 and 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_536_ua_en", "question": "Mendoza was twinned with which city between 1986 and 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_537_ua_en", "question": "Bila Tserkva was twinned with which city from 1980 to 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_538_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Funchal between 1959 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_539_ua_en", "question": "Dnipro was twinned with which city between 1961 and 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_540_ua_en", "question": "Lisbon was twinned with which city between 1959 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_541_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Tel Aviv from 1930 to 1935?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_542_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Seoul from 1934 to 1939?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_543_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Almaty between 1960 and 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_544_ua_en", "question": "Mie Prefecture was twinned with which city from 1959 to 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_545_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Coimbra between 1962 and 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_546_ua_en", "question": "Guangzhou was twinned with which city from 1978 to 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_547_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Naha from 1937 to 1942?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_548_ua_en", "question": "Abidjan was twinned with which city from 1948 to 1953?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_549_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Budapest from 1964 to 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_550_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Donetsk between 1957 and 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_551_ua_en", "question": "What was the twinned city of Tallinn from 1941 to 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_552_ua_en", "question": "What military rank did Pavel Shuvalov have in the year of 1907?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_553_ua_en", "question": "What military rank did Andrei Grechko have during 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_554_ua_en", "question": "What military rank did Captain Nazi have between 1985 and 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_555_ua_en", "question": "What was the military rank of Pierre Henri Hugoniot during 1889?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_556_ua_en", "question": "What was the military rank of Rumen Radev between 1978 and 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_557_ua_en", "question": "What military rank did Alexander Yefimov have in 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_558_ua_en", "question": "What was the military rank of David Dragunsky during 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_559_ua_en", "question": "What was the military rank of Sergey Denisov during 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_560_ua_en", "question": "What was the military rank of Vladimir Ilyushin in 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_561_ua_en", "question": "What military rank did Alexander Molodchy have during 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_562_ua_en", "question": "What was the military rank of August von Werder in 1889?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_563_ua_en", "question": "What military rank did Vladimir Arsenyev have in the year of 1932?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_564_ua_en", "question": "What military rank did Alexander III of Russia have in the year of 1896?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_565_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Heather Mills between 1993 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_566_ua_en", "question": "Who was Maureen Starkey Tigrett 's spouse during 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_567_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Hildegard of Vinzgouw in 785?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_568_ua_en", "question": "Who was Freddie Stroma 's spouse between 2006 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_569_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Christina Hendricks between 1995 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_570_ua_en", "question": "Who was Linda McCartney 's spouse during 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_571_ua_en", "question": "Who was Emma Heming Willis 's spouse between 1998 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_572_ua_en", "question": "Who was Desiderata of the Lombards 's spouse in 778?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_573_ua_en", "question": "Who was Carrie Fisher 's spouse during 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_574_ua_en", "question": "Who was Fastrada 's spouse during 796?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_575_ua_en", "question": "Who was Fastrada 's spouse during 796?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_576_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Lisa Marie Presley between 1954 and 1959?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_577_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Barbara Bach from 1975 to 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_578_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Hildegard of Vinzgouw during 785?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_579_ua_en", "question": "Who was Josh Blaylock 's spouse between 1998 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_580_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of David Furnish between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_581_ua_en", "question": "Who was Maria Shriver 's spouse from 1971 to 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_582_ua_en", "question": "Who was Carrie Fisher 's spouse during 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_583_ua_en", "question": "Who was Casimir Dudevant 's spouse in the year of 1873?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_584_ua_en", "question": "Who was Sonia Orwell 's spouse in 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_585_ua_en", "question": "Who was Daniella Pick 's spouse from 2009 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_586_ua_en", "question": "Who was Margot Honecker 's spouse in 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_587_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Debbie Rowe between 1981 and 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_588_ua_en", "question": "Who was Olivia Harrison 's spouse between 1970 and 1975?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_589_ua_en", "question": "Who was Claudia Schiffer 's spouse from 1992 to 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_590_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Edie Brickell between 1979 and 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_591_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Pattie Boyd from 1957 to 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_592_ua_en", "question": "Who was Queen Paola of Belgium 's spouse between 1948 and 1953?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_593_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Demi Moore from 1947 to 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_594_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Galina Lukashenko between 1969 and 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_595_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Princess Hermine Reuss of Greiz during 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_596_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Anna Magdalena Bach in 1762?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_597_ua_en", "question": "Who was Julia Domna 's spouse in 219?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_598_ua_en", "question": "Who was David Thornton 's spouse between 1977 and 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_599_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Maria Barbara Bach during 1722?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_600_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Poppaea Sabina during 67?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_601_ua_en", "question": "Who was Fanny Stevenson 's spouse during 1916?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_602_ua_en", "question": "Who was Fanny Stevenson 's spouse during 1916?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_603_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Mirka Federer from 2000 to 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_604_ua_en", "question": "Who was Claudia Octavia 's spouse in 64?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_605_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Nadezhda Krupskaya during 1941?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_606_ua_en", "question": "Who was the spouse of Cosima Wagner in the year of 1932?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_607_ua_en", "question": "Who was Statilia Messalina 's spouse between 54 and 59?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_608_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team South Korea national football team from 2004 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_609_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Inter Milan between 1948 and 1953?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_610_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Vissel Kobe from 1968 to 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_611_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team MSV Duisburg between 2002 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_612_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team FC Zenit Saint Petersburg between 1980 and 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_613_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Austria national association football team from 2009 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_614_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team CF Fuenlabrada from 2000 to 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_615_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team FC Kariya from 1992 to 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_616_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team VfL Wolfsburg between 2005 and 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_617_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Maria Sharapova between 1993 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_618_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team FC Erzgebirge Aue between 1914 and 1919?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_619_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Inter Milan between 1988 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_620_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team PSV Eindhoven from 1991 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_621_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Maria Sharapova between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_622_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team AC Milan between 1953 and 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_623_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team FC Erzgebirge Aue between 1926 and 1931?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_624_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team RB Leipzig from 2003 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_625_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team AS Monaco FC between 1986 and 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_626_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team OGC Nice from 2012 to 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_627_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Vissel Kobe between 1984 and 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_628_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Kei Nishikori from 2001 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_629_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Saudi Arabia national football team between 2012 and 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_630_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Andy Roddick from 1992 to 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_631_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team VfB Stuttgart between 1983 and 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_632_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Andy Murray from 1997 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_633_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Italy national association football team between 1981 and 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_634_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team RC Strasbourg from 1991 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_635_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Hertha BSC from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_636_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team FC Bayern Munich from 1962 to 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_637_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team VfB Stuttgart II from 2012 to 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_638_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Hertha BSC between 1985 and 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_639_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Scotland national football team between 1975 and 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_640_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Juventus FC between 1962 and 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_641_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Eintracht Frankfurt from 1886 to 1891?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_642_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Qhubeka Assos from 1981 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_643_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team VfB Stuttgart from 1997 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_644_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team SK Sturm Graz between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_645_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Eintracht Frankfurt between 1896 and 1901?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_646_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Poland national association football team from 1898 to 1903?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_647_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Austria national association football team from 2006 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_648_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Tennis Borussia Berlin between 1962 and 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_649_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Tennis Borussia Berlin between 1987 and 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_650_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Juventus FC from 1985 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_651_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Ukraine national association football team from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_652_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Czech Republic national association football team between 1982 and 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_653_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team AC Milan between 1960 and 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_654_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Armenia national football team between 1965 and 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_655_ua_en", "question": "Who was the head coach of the team Clube de Regatas do Flamengo from 2011 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_656_ua_en", "question": "Who coached the team Italy national association football team between 1976 and 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_657_ua_en", "question": "What was the occupation of Osei Bonsu during 1826?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_658_ua_en", "question": "What was the occupation of Francesco II Sforza in 1537?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_659_ua_en", "question": "What was Francesco II Sforza 's occupation in the year of 1537?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_660_ua_en", "question": "What was Reginfrid 's occupation in 816?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_661_ua_en", "question": "What was Idris Alooma 's occupation in 1598?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_662_ua_en", "question": "What was Prempeh II 's occupation during 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_663_ua_en", "question": "What was Naruhito 's occupation between 2007 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_664_ua_en", "question": "What was Harald Klak 's occupation during 846?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_665_ua_en", "question": "What was the occupation of Harald Klak in the year of 846?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_666_ua_en", "question": "What was the occupation of Beatrix of the Netherlands between 1969 and 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_667_ua_en", "question": "What was Henry VIII of England 's occupation during 1549?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_668_ua_en", "question": "What was Constantine II of Greece 's occupation from 1958 to 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_669_ua_en", "question": "What was Judith of Bavaria 's occupation during 845?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_670_ua_en", "question": "What was the occupation of Hemming of Denmark in the year of 814?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_671_ua_en", "question": "What was Harald V of Norway 's occupation between 1978 and 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_672_ua_en", "question": "What was the occupation of Osei Tutu in 1719?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_673_ua_en", "question": "What was William Herschel 's occupation in 1824?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_674_ua_en", "question": "What was Henri Joseph Anastase Perrotin 's occupation in the year of 1906?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_675_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Chief Executive of Hong Kong between 1960 and 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_676_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of General Secretary of the Communist Party from 2005 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_677_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Chairman of the Central Military Commission of the Chinese Communist Party from 1897 to 1902?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_678_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of mayor of Beijing from 1897 to 1902?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_679_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Prime Minister of Belgium between 1817 and 1822?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_680_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Chief Executive of Hong Kong from 1968 to 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_681_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of General Secretary of the Chinese Communist Party between 1966 and 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_682_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Prime Minister of Belgium between 1819 and 1824?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_683_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of President of Ukraine from 1985 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_684_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of General Secretary of the Chinese Communist Party from 1956 to 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_685_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of President of the Royal Astronomical Society from 1791 to 1796?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_686_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Federal Minister of Finance between 1932 and 1937?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_687_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Chairman of the Central Military Commission of the Chinese Communist Party between 1946 and 1951?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_688_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Grand Prince of Kiev between 858 and 863?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_689_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of President of the Royal Astronomical Society between 1812 and 1817?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_690_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Leader of the Christian Democratic Union from 1929 to 1934?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_691_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of President of the European Commission from 1934 to 1939?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_692_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of mayor of Shanghai from 1908 to 1913?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_693_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Lucasian Professor of Mathematics between 1971 and 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_694_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of member of the Politburo of the Chinese Communist Party from 1977 to 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_695_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of member of the Politburo of the Chinese Communist Party from 1981 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_696_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of mayor of Shanghai from 1920 to 1925?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_697_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of mayor of Beijing between 1890 and 1895?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_698_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of President of the European Council between 1997 and 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_699_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of President of Finland between 2004 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_700_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of count of Holland from 1587 to 1592?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_701_ua_en", "question": "Who was the office holder of Secretary for Education from 1991 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_702_ua_en", "question": "Who directed or managed Fraunhofer Society from 1943 to 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_703_ua_en", "question": "Who was the director or manager of Guards Corps from 1807 to 1812?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_704_ua_en", "question": "Who directed or managed Max Planck Institute for Mathematics from 1966 to 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_705_ua_en", "question": "Abwehr was managed or directed by whom in the year of 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_706_ua_en", "question": "Who directed or managed CERN from 1934 to 1939?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_707_ua_en", "question": "Who was the director or manager of Koenigsberg Observatory in 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_708_ua_en", "question": "Who directed or managed Institute for Peace Research and Security Policy at the University of Hamburg between 1972 and 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_709_ua_en", "question": "European Southern Observatory was managed or directed by whom between 1956 and 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_710_ua_en", "question": "German General Staff was managed or directed by whom between 1839 and 1844?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_711_ua_en", "question": "Who was the director or manager of Egyptian Museum of Berlin from 1820 to 1825?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_712_ua_en", "question": "Who was the director or manager of Seeberg Observatory from 1773 to 1778?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_713_ua_en", "question": "Who was the director or manager of Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences from 1925 to 1930?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_714_ua_en", "question": "Jewish Museum Berlin was managed or directed by whom from 1982 to 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_715_ua_en", "question": "Regensburger Domspatzen was managed or directed by whom between 1950 and 1955?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_716_ua_en", "question": "Federal Intelligence Service was managed or directed by whom from 1942 to 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_717_ua_en", "question": "Who was the director or manager of Robert Koch Institute between 1875 and 1880?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_718_ua_en", "question": "Who directed or managed Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences between 1928 and 1933?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_719_ua_en", "question": "Who was the director or manager of Dachau concentration camp in 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_720_ua_en", "question": "European Union shared border with what from 1949 to 1954?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_721_ua_en", "question": "What did European Union share border with from 1947 to 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_722_ua_en", "question": "What did Czechoslovakia share border with in the year of 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_723_ua_en", "question": "Czechoslovakia shared border with what in 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_724_ua_en", "question": "What did Yugoslavia share border with in 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_725_ua_en", "question": "What did Latvia share border with between 1903 and 1908?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_726_ua_en", "question": "What did Arab League share border with from 1926 to 1931?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_727_ua_en", "question": "What did Confederate States share border with in 1867?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_728_ua_en", "question": "What did Neutral Moresnet share border with during 1922?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_729_ua_en", "question": "What did Arab League share border with between 1928 and 1933?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_730_ua_en", "question": "What did Turkey share border with between 1910 and 1915?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_731_ua_en", "question": "Estonia shared border with what between 1979 and 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_732_ua_en", "question": "What did Latvia share border with from 1976 to 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_733_ua_en", "question": "What did Turkey share border with from 1917 to 1922?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_734_ua_en", "question": "Germany shared border with what from 1902 to 1907?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_735_ua_en", "question": "Virginia shared border with what from 1772 to 1777?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_736_ua_en", "question": "Tajikistan shared border with what from 1872 to 1877?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_737_ua_en", "question": "What did Virginia share border with from 1781 to 1786?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_738_ua_en", "question": "What did Estonia share border with between 1977 and 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_739_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Constantinople since in 319?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_740_ua_en", "question": "South Australia was replaced by what since in 1823?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_741_ua_en", "question": "South Australia was replaced by what since during 1824?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_742_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Nazi Germany since in 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_743_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Landespolizei since in the year of 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_744_ua_en", "question": "German Democratic Republic was replaced by what since in 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_745_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Viken since in the year of 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_746_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Viken since during 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_747_ua_en", "question": "canton of France was replaced by what since in the year of 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_748_ua_en", "question": "Hombleux was replaced by what since in the year of 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_749_ua_en", "question": "universal time was replaced by what since in the year of 1914?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_750_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Scottish council area since in 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_751_ua_en", "question": "Indonesia was replaced by what since in the year of 1937?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_752_ua_en", "question": "Englon was replaced by what since during 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_753_ua_en", "question": "Nazi Germany was replaced by what since during 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_754_ua_en", "question": "Alfa Romeo Racing was replaced by what since in the year of 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_755_ua_en", "question": "Scuderia AlphaTauri was replaced by what since during 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_756_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Porvoo since in 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_757_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Jordan since in 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_758_ua_en", "question": "International Community Radio Taipei was replaced by what since in the year of 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_759_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Avranches since in the year of 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_760_ua_en", "question": "Supreme Tribunal of Justice of Venezuela in exile was replaced by what since in 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_761_ua_en", "question": "Charleroi was replaced by what since during 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_762_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Viatris since in 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_763_ua_en", "question": "British Army of the Rhine was replaced by what since in the year of 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_764_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Northern Territory since in the year of 1897?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_765_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Gustave Eiffel University since during 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_766_ua_en", "question": "Dampierre was replaced by what since in the year of 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_767_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Siikalatva since during 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_768_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Sastamala since in the year of 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_769_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Fontain since in the year of 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_770_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Sastamala since in 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_771_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Rouillac since in the year of 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_772_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Khanate of Kokand since in 1878?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_773_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Nanchez since in the year of 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_774_ua_en", "question": "BBC News was replaced by what since in the year of 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_775_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Les Belleville since in the year of 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_776_ua_en", "question": "Soviet Olympic Committee was replaced by what since in 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_777_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Charleroi since during 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_778_ua_en", "question": "What manufactured Common Booster Core from 1986 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_779_ua_en", "question": "What manufactured Delta between 1944 and 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_780_ua_en", "question": "What manufactured Mitsubishi Proudia from 2005 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_781_ua_en", "question": "What manufactured Pentium D between 1992 and 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_782_ua_en", "question": "What manufactured Atlas II between 1984 and 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_783_ua_en", "question": "What was the manufacturer of Atlas IIAS between 1973 and 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_784_ua_en", "question": "What manufactured Isuzu Gemini between 1958 and 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_785_ua_en", "question": "What was the manufacturer of Atlas IIA between 1982 and 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_786_ua_en", "question": "What was the manufacturer of Mitsubishi ASX from 2010 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_787_ua_en", "question": "What manufactured Mitsubishi Dignity from 2004 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_788_ua_en", "question": "What manufactured Suzuki Landy from 1996 to 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_789_ua_en", "question": "What was the manufacturer of Nissan Livina from 1993 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_790_ua_en", "question": "What was the manufacturer of Nissan Livina between 1994 and 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_791_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Rabat between 1896 and 1901?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_792_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Manila from 1967 to 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_793_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Zomba between 1865 and 1870?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_794_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Bujumbura between 1953 and 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_795_ua_en", "question": "Abuja was the capital of what from 1985 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_796_ua_en", "question": "Manila was the capital of what between 1923 and 1928?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_797_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Brazzaville from 1893 to 1898?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_798_ua_en", "question": "Taipei was the capital of what between 1881 and 1886?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_799_ua_en", "question": "Ashgabat was the capital of what from 1865 to 1870?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_800_ua_en", "question": "Damascus was the capital of what between 1939 and 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_801_ua_en", "question": "Kinshasa was the capital of what from 1954 to 1959?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_802_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Aden from 2000 to 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_803_ua_en", "question": "Dushanbe was the capital of what from 1914 to 1919?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_804_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Salem from 1847 to 1852?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_805_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Riyadh from 1810 to 1815?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_806_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Jerusalem between 1940 and 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_807_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Ciudad de la Paz from 2008 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_808_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Islamabad from 1955 to 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_809_ua_en", "question": "Malabo was the capital of what from 1956 to 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_810_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Gitega between 2007 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_811_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Nicosia between 1952 and 1957?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_812_ua_en", "question": "Riga was the capital of what from 1984 to 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_813_ua_en", "question": "Ljubljana was the capital of what between 1979 and 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_814_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Tokyo from 1843 to 1848?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_815_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Bern from 1833 to 1838?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_816_ua_en", "question": "Edo was the capital of what during 1870?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_817_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Berlin from 1981 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_818_ua_en", "question": "Cahaba was the capital of what between 1813 and 1818?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_819_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Turin from 1805 to 1810?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_820_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Vichy between 1929 and 1934?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_821_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Accra between 1871 and 1876?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_822_ua_en", "question": "Tokyo Prefecture was the capital of what in the year of 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_823_ua_en", "question": "Montevideo was the capital of what between 1820 and 1825?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_824_ua_en", "question": "Ankara was the capital of what from 1916 to 1921?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_825_ua_en", "question": "Annapolis was the capital of what between 1684 and 1689?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_826_ua_en", "question": "Coimbra was the capital of what between 1117 and 1122?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_827_ua_en", "question": "Bonn was the capital of what from 1935 to 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_828_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Tuscaloosa between 1816 and 1821?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_829_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Quebec City from 1858 to 1863?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_830_ua_en", "question": "Rio de Janeiro was the capital of what between 1755 and 1760?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_831_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Tokyo City in the year of 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_832_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Helsinki between 1793 and 1798?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_833_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Vallejo between 1844 and 1849?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_834_ua_en", "question": "Prague was the capital of what from 1905 to 1910?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_835_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of New York City between 1772 and 1777?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_836_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Belfast between 1906 and 1911?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_837_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Dublin from 1779 to 1784?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_838_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Kyoto between 783 and 788?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_839_ua_en", "question": "San Jose was the capital of what from 1835 to 1840?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_840_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Philadelphia between 1779 and 1784?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_841_ua_en", "question": "Budapest was the capital of what from 1914 to 1919?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_842_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Kutaisi from 2004 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_843_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Stockholm between 1425 and 1430?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_844_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Auckland between 1833 and 1838?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_845_ua_en", "question": "Ngerulmud was the capital of what between 1997 and 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_846_ua_en", "question": "Quito was the capital of what between 1817 and 1822?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_847_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of New Delhi from 1891 to 1896?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_848_ua_en", "question": "Pyongyang was the capital of what from 1940 to 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_849_ua_en", "question": "Tegucigalpa was the capital of what between 1867 and 1872?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_850_ua_en", "question": "Augusta was the capital of what from 1817 to 1822?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_851_ua_en", "question": "Kolonia was the capital of what between 1971 and 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_852_ua_en", "question": "What was the capital of Melbourne from 1806 to 1811?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_853_ua_en", "question": "Where was Dakar Rally located from 1971 to 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_854_ua_en", "question": "Where was United Rugby Championship located between 1994 and 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_855_ua_en", "question": "Dakar Rally took place in which location between 1964 and 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_856_ua_en", "question": "Central Group of Forces took place in which location between 1936 and 1941?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_857_ua_en", "question": "Where was United Rugby Championship taking place from 1973 to 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_858_ua_en", "question": "Where was Central Group of Forces taking place between 1930 and 1935?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_859_ua_en", "question": "Where was Wiki Education Foundation located between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_860_ua_en", "question": "Black Death took place in which location from 1327 to 1332?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_861_ua_en", "question": "Where was Songs of David Byrne and Brian Eno Tour taking place from 1997 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_862_ua_en", "question": "Where was Goddard Institute for Space Studies taking place from 1949 to 1954?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_863_ua_en", "question": "Songs of David Byrne and Brian Eno Tour took place in which location between 1994 and 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_864_ua_en", "question": "Where was Normandy Format located between 2008 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_865_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by European Union between 1932 and 1937?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_866_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by European Union between 1945 and 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_867_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by German Confederation in 1868?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_868_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by United Kingdom between 1914 and 1919?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_869_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by United States of America between 1781 and 1786?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_870_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by United States of America between 1756 and 1761?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_871_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Confederate States during 1867?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_872_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by District of Columbia from 1771 to 1776?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_873_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Germany from 1930 to 1935?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_874_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by District of Columbia from 1780 to 1785?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_875_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Yvelines between 1953 and 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_876_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Lille metropolis between 1957 and 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_877_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Yvelines between 1958 and 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_878_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by German Confederation during 1868?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_879_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by West Sumatra from 1944 to 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_880_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by West Sumatra between 1947 and 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_881_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Kuusiokunnat between 1981 and 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_882_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Kuusiokunnat between 1985 and 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_883_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Suupohja between 1987 and 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_884_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Suupohja between 1983 and 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_885_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by West Germany during 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_886_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by Germany between 1944 and 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_887_ua_en", "question": "What administrative territorial was acquired by West Germany in the year of 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_888_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Gian Piero Ventura from 1964 to 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_889_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Peter Bosz from 2006 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_890_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Ottavio Bianchi from 1947 to 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_891_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Marco Giampaolo between 1953 and 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_892_ua_en", "question": "Andrea Pirlo was the coach of which team between 2009 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_893_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Arrigo Sacchi from 1958 to 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_894_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Dino Zoff between 1974 and 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_895_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Marcello Lippi between 1963 and 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_896_ua_en", "question": "Antonio Conte was the coach of which team between 1988 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_897_ua_en", "question": "Eugenio Bersellini was the coach of which team in 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_898_ua_en", "question": "Giuseppe Meazza was the coach of which team in 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_899_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Laurent Blanc between 1998 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_900_ua_en", "question": "Arrigo Sacchi was the coach of which team between 1963 and 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_901_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Antonio Conte from 1996 to 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_902_ua_en", "question": "Walter Zenga was the coach of which team from 1990 to 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_903_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Didier Deschamps from 1980 to 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_904_ua_en", "question": "Eugenio Bersellini was the coach of which team in 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_905_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Fabio Capello from 1962 to 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_906_ua_en", "question": "Armando Castellazzi was the coach of which team during 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_907_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Simone Inzaghi from 2006 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_908_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Helenio Herrera in the year of 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_909_ua_en", "question": "Carlo Ancelotti was the coach of which team from 1964 to 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_910_ua_en", "question": "Stefano Pioli was the coach of which team between 1974 and 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_911_ua_en", "question": "Luciano Spalletti was the coach of which team from 1985 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_912_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Claudio Ranieri from 1963 to 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_913_ua_en", "question": "Giovanni Trapattoni was the coach of which team between 1965 and 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_914_ua_en", "question": "Roberto Mancini was the coach of which team from 1975 to 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_915_ua_en", "question": "Claudio Ranieri was the coach of which team from 1975 to 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_916_ua_en", "question": "Walter Mazzarri was the coach of which team between 1978 and 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_917_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Luciano Spalletti from 1984 to 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_918_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Marcello Lippi from 1958 to 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_919_ua_en", "question": "Eusebio Di Francesco was the coach of which team from 1984 to 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_920_ua_en", "question": "Andrea Pirlo was the coach of which team from 1988 to 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_921_ua_en", "question": "Massimiliano Allegri was the coach of which team from 1981 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_922_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Luigi Simoni during 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_923_ua_en", "question": "Angelo Alessio was the coach of which team between 2003 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_924_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Frank de Boer from 1994 to 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_925_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Sylvinho between 2005 and 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_926_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Massimiliano Allegri between 1986 and 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_927_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Fabio Grosso between 2009 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_928_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Giuseppe Meazza in the year of 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_929_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Helenio Herrera in the year of 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_930_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Roy Hodgson between 1966 and 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_931_ua_en", "question": "Giovanni Trapattoni was the coach of which team from 1952 to 1957?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_932_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Luigi Radice in 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_933_ua_en", "question": "Fabrizio Ravanelli was the coach of which team between 2002 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_934_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Maurizio Sarri between 1984 and 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_935_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Vincenzo Montella from 2000 to 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_936_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Roberto Mancini between 1979 and 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_937_ua_en", "question": "Roy Hodgson was the coach of which team from 1925 to 1930?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_938_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Walter Mazzarri between 1984 and 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_939_ua_en", "question": "Thiago Motta was the coach of which team between 2006 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_940_ua_en", "question": "Thiago Motta was the coach of which team from 2010 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_941_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Rolando Maran from 1990 to 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_942_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Ottavio Bianchi between 1962 and 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_943_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Andriy Shevchenko between 2001 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_944_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Vincenzo Montella from 2003 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_945_ua_en", "question": "Luigi Radice was the coach of which team in 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_946_ua_en", "question": "Nedo Sonetti was the coach of which team between 1960 and 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_947_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Andrea Mandorlini from 1970 to 1975?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_948_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Nedo Sonetti between 1967 and 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_949_ua_en", "question": "Aldo Agroppi was the coach of which team between 1956 and 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_950_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Stefano Pioli from 1974 to 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_951_ua_en", "question": "Which team was coached by Diego Pablo Simeone from 1963 to 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_952_ua_en", "question": "Franco Scoglio was the coach of which team in 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_953_ua_en", "question": "Franco Scoglio was the coach of which team during 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_954_ua_en", "question": "Rolando Maran was the coach of which team from 1987 to 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_955_ua_en", "question": "Aurelio Andreazzoli was the coach of which team from 2004 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_956_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Russi Taylor in 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_957_ua_en", "question": "Leslie Jones published which notable work between 2005 and 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_958_ua_en", "question": "Benjamin Henry Latrobe published which notable work during 1822?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_959_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Owen Wilson between 1994 and 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_960_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Holly Robinson Peete between 1974 and 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_961_ua_en", "question": "Savannah Guthrie published which notable work between 2003 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_962_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Al Roker between 1987 and 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_963_ua_en", "question": "Barbara Walters published which notable work between 1949 and 1954?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_964_ua_en", "question": "Tamron Hall published which notable work between 2007 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_965_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Katie Couric from 1981 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_966_ua_en", "question": "Frank McGee published which notable work during 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_967_ua_en", "question": "Meredith Vieira published which notable work between 1957 and 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_968_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Seth Rogen from 1999 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_969_ua_en", "question": "Hoda Kotb published which notable work from 1994 to 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_970_ua_en", "question": "James Earl Jones published which notable work between 1987 and 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_971_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Arianna Huffington from 1999 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_972_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Russell T Davies between 1992 and 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_973_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Lennon Stella from 2005 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_974_ua_en", "question": "David Bates Douglass published which notable work in 1851?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_975_ua_en", "question": "Sara Gilbert published which notable work between 1996 and 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_976_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by John Cleese between 1986 and 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_977_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Dylan Sprouse between 1990 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_978_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Cole Sprouse from 1993 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_979_ua_en", "question": "Geoffrey Rush published which notable work from 1989 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_980_ua_en", "question": "Ferdinand Boberg published which notable work in the year of 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_981_ua_en", "question": "Heather Locklear published which notable work from 1987 to 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_982_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Connie Britton between 1988 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_983_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Ellen DeGeneres between 1988 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_984_ua_en", "question": "Morley Safer published which notable work in 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_985_ua_en", "question": "Mike Wallace published which notable work in 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_986_ua_en", "question": "Meredith Vieira published which notable work between 1974 and 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_987_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Shannen Doherty between 1976 and 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_988_ua_en", "question": "Vanessa Marcil published which notable work between 1965 and 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_989_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Tyra Banks between 1989 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_990_ua_en", "question": "William Shatner published which notable work between 1972 and 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_991_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Heather Locklear from 1976 to 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_992_ua_en", "question": "Barbara Walters published which notable work between 1942 and 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_993_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Luigi Cagnola in 1835?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_994_ua_en", "question": "NHK published which notable work from 1944 to 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_995_ua_en", "question": "Kourtney Kardashian published which notable work between 2000 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_996_ua_en", "question": "Andrzej Pszenicki published which notable work in the year of 1943?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_997_ua_en", "question": "Rob Kardashian published which notable work from 2001 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_998_ua_en", "question": "Piero Portaluppi published which notable work in the year of 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_999_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Naya Rivera in 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1000_ua_en", "question": "Kris Jenner published which notable work between 1993 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1001_ua_en", "question": "Scott Disick published which notable work from 1995 to 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1002_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Alyssa Milano between 1989 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1003_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Holly Marie Combs between 1992 and 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1004_ua_en", "question": "Rose McGowan published which notable work between 1989 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1005_ua_en", "question": "Frank Welker published which notable work between 1963 and 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1006_ua_en", "question": "Tamara Taylor published which notable work between 1994 and 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1007_ua_en", "question": "Don Messick published which notable work during 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1008_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Matthew Lillard between 2003 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1009_ua_en", "question": "Charles Jennens published which notable work in 1775?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1010_ua_en", "question": "China Anne McClain published which notable work between 1998 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1011_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Candice Bergen between 1995 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1012_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Zendaya from 1995 to 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1013_ua_en", "question": "Rollan Martirosov published which notable work during 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1014_ua_en", "question": "Everett Rogers published which notable work in 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1015_ua_en", "question": "Which notable work was published by Nippon Broadcasting System between 1961 and 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1016_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Stadio Olimpico Grande Torino between 1912 and 1917?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1017_ua_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Stadio Olimpico Grande Torino from 1918 to 1923?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1018_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Giuseppe Meazza Stadium from 1913 to 1918?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1019_ua_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Stadio Olimpico from 1945 to 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1020_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Stadio Olimpico from 1942 to 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1021_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Stadio delle Alpi in the year of 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1022_ua_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Stadio delle Alpi in the year of 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1023_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Stadio Flaminio from 1964 to 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1024_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Stadio Flaminio from 1905 to 1910?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1025_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Giuseppe Meazza Stadium between 1916 and 1921?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1026_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied One Times Square from 1890 to 1895?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1027_ua_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Birthplace of Richard Nixon between 1907 and 1912?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1028_ua_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of RAF Burtonwood in the year of 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1029_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Arsenal Stadium in 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1030_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Barnet Copthall from 2004 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1031_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied MEK Compound from 1978 to 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1032_ua_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Fort Frederiksborg from 1642 to 1647?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1033_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Marlborough House between 1954 and 1959?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1034_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Eurotower from 1956 to 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1035_ua_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Cape Coast Castle from 1640 to 1645?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1036_ua_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Montjuic Olympic Stadium between 1979 and 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1037_ua_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Royal Palace of Amsterdam between 1802 and 1807?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1038_ua_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Stadio Alberto Braglia from 1996 to 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1039_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Rembrandt House Museum from 1629 to 1634?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1040_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Anfield between 1877 and 1882?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1041_ua_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Braunes Haus during 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1042_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Montjuic Olympic Stadium from 2010 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1043_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Charlottenhof Palace between 1820 and 1825?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1044_ua_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Einsteinhaus between 1889 and 1894?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1045_ua_en", "question": "Who occupied Bolshiye Gorki from 1903 to 1908?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1046_ua_en", "question": "Who was the occupant of Berghof in 1954?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1047_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of World Union for Progressive Judaism was located in where from 1903 to 1908?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1048_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of Fawcett Publications was located in where from 1909 to 1914?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1049_ua_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Automobile Manufacturers Association located during 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1050_ua_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Erie Railroad located during 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1051_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of College Art Association was located in where from 2005 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1052_ua_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Fleischer Studios located in 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1053_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of Foot Locker was located in where from 2006 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1054_ua_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Doghouse Records located between 1979 and 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1055_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of American Petroleum Institute was located in where between 1912 and 1917?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1056_ua_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Standard Oil located during 1913?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1057_ua_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Nickelodeon Animation Studio located between 1975 and 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1058_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of MetLife was located in where between 1898 and 1903?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1059_ua_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of American Association for Justice located from 1967 to 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1060_ua_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of United Aircraft and Transport Corporation located during 1936?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1061_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of United States Census Bureau was located in where between 1890 and 1895?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1062_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of American Petroleum Institute was located in where from 1912 to 1917?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1063_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of Code for America was located in where from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1064_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of Code for America was located in where between 2006 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1065_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of Port Authority of New York and New Jersey was located in where from 1961 to 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1066_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of Port Authority of New York and New Jersey was located in where from 1963 to 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1067_ua_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Air Force Global Strike Command located between 1938 and 1943?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1068_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of United States Department of Commerce was located in where between 1918 and 1923?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1069_ua_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Supreme Court of the United States located between 1844 and 1849?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1070_ua_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of Gallup located between 1991 and 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1071_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of Washington Spirit was located in where from 2004 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1072_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of Mozilla Corporation was located in where between 2014 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1073_ua_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of China Zhi Gong Party located between 1919 and 1924?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1074_ua_en", "question": "The headquarter of SVB Financial Group was located in where from 1959 to 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1075_ua_en", "question": "Where was the headquarter of The Baffler located from 1966 to 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1076_ua_en", "question": "Who performed M between 1985 and 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1077_ua_en", "question": "Who performed M between 1956 and 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1078_ua_en", "question": "Who performed Lord Voldemort in the year of 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1079_ua_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Shaggy Rogers between 1932 and 1937?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1080_ua_en", "question": "Who performed Q between 1951 and 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1081_ua_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Princess Protection Program from 2003 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1082_ua_en", "question": "Another Cinderella Story was performed by whom from 1994 to 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1083_ua_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Greg Heffley between 2001 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1084_ua_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Linda Perry between 1974 and 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1085_ua_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Lord Voldemort during 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1086_ua_en", "question": "Who performed Lola Bunny from 1983 to 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1087_ua_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Hello Kitty between 1983 and 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1088_ua_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Winnie the Pooh from 1975 to 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1089_ua_en", "question": "Mickey Mouse was performed by whom from 2000 to 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1090_ua_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Gopher between 1957 and 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1091_ua_en", "question": "Q was performed by whom from 1999 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1092_ua_en", "question": "Who performed Donald Duck between 1925 and 1930?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1093_ua_en", "question": "Who performed Lola Bunny from 1974 to 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1094_ua_en", "question": "Who performed Gomez Addams from 1958 to 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1095_ua_en", "question": "Who performed Mac Tonight between 1974 and 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1096_ua_en", "question": "Who performed Oscar the Grouch between 1956 and 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1097_ua_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Scooter between 1965 and 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1098_ua_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Luigi between 1977 and 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1099_ua_en", "question": "Who was the performer of Doctor Eggman between 1979 and 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1100_ua_en", "question": "Winnie the Pooh was performed by whom between 1951 and 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1101_ua_en", "question": "Who performed Donald Duck between 1900 and 1905?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1102_ua_en", "question": "Pluto was performed by whom from 1919 to 1924?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1103_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Pangyo Station between 2005 and 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1104_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Migeum Station between 1980 and 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1105_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Wangsimni Station between 1892 and 1897?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1106_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Wangsimni Station from 1905 to 1910?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1107_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Tai Po Kau railway station between 1903 and 1908?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1108_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Sinnonhyeon Station from 2011 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1109_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Ori Station from 1979 to 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1110_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Yangjae Station between 1969 and 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1111_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Bojeong Station from 1998 to 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1112_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Ori Station from 1976 to 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1113_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Jukjeon Station between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1114_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Jeongja Station from 1981 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1115_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Jeongja Station from 1983 to 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1116_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Dongcheon Station between 2004 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1117_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Pangyo Station between 2003 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1118_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Imae Station between 1997 and 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1119_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Imae Station between 1989 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1120_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Gangnam Station from 1944 to 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1121_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Nonhyeon Station from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1122_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Yoyogi Station from 1994 to 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1123_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Songjiazhuang station between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1124_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Jamsil Station from 1967 to 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1125_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Jamsil Station from 1959 to 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1126_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Gongzhufen station from 1962 to 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1127_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Cishou Si station from 2006 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1128_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Keisei Tsudanuma Station from 1914 to 1919?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1129_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Nonhyeon Station from 2014 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1130_ua_en", "question": "Which station was adjacent to Yangjae Station from 1973 to 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1131_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Gangnam Station between 1969 and 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1132_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Sosa Station between 2010 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1133_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Sinsa Station between 2007 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1134_ua_en", "question": "What was the adjacent station of Sinnonhyeon Station from 2010 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1135_ua_en", "question": "WWE NXT was presented by whom from 2012 to 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1136_ua_en", "question": "Robot Wars was presented by whom between 1984 and 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1137_ua_en", "question": "Who was the presenter of The Late Show with Stephen Colbert from 2003 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1138_ua_en", "question": "The Daily Show Mondays with Jon Stewart was presented by whom from 1989 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1139_ua_en", "question": "The Colbert Report was presented by whom from 1996 to 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1140_ua_en", "question": "The Daily Show Mondays with Jon Stewart was presented by whom between 1988 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1141_ua_en", "question": "Top Gear was presented by whom between 1988 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1142_ua_en", "question": "Who was the presenter of Sportschau between 1954 and 1959?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1143_ua_en", "question": "Sportschau was presented by whom between 1956 and 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1144_ua_en", "question": "Tagesthemen was presented by whom from 1969 to 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1145_ua_en", "question": "Today was presented by whom from 1940 to 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1146_ua_en", "question": "To Tell the Truth was presented by whom between 2010 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1147_ua_en", "question": "Top Gear was presented by whom between 1995 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1148_ua_en", "question": "Who was the presenter of Card Sharks from 2006 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1149_ua_en", "question": "Who was the presenter of The Tonight Show from 1925 to 1930?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1150_ua_en", "question": "Who was the presenter of The Tonight Show between 1935 and 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1151_ua_en", "question": "The Voice of Germany was presented by whom from 2004 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1152_ua_en", "question": "Who was the presenter of Tagesthemen from 1956 to 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1153_ua_en", "question": "Who was the presenter of The Late Late Show with James Corden between 1964 and 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1154_ua_en", "question": "Where was Emile Guillemin exhibited in the year of 1909?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1155_ua_en", "question": "Where was Madonna of Jacob Floreins exhibited from 1978 to 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1156_ua_en", "question": "Where was Antonio Rotta exhibited during 1905?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1157_ua_en", "question": "Where was The Return of the Prodigal Son exhibited from 1761 to 1766?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1158_ua_en", "question": "Where was Boxer at Rest exhibited between 2002 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1159_ua_en", "question": "nihonium was named after what between 2006 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1160_ua_en", "question": "Washington was named after what from 1827 to 1832?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1161_ua_en", "question": "Lincoln was named after what between 1852 and 1857?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1162_ua_en", "question": "Pariser Platz was named after what from 1802 to 1807?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1163_ua_en", "question": "Lincoln was named after what between 1845 and 1850?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1164_ua_en", "question": "Central do Brasil was named after what from 1877 to 1882?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1165_ua_en", "question": "hydrogen was named after what from 1776 to 1781?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1166_ua_en", "question": "Chornomorsk was named after what from 1939 to 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1167_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Niels in 1136?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1168_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Tristan in 587?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1169_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of George I of Great Britain during 1729?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1170_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Saban from 225 to 230?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1171_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Christian IX of Denmark in the year of 1908?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1172_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Daru during 79?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1173_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Giru in 130?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1174_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Gaeru in 168?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1175_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Goi in the year of 288?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1176_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Gusu during 236?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1177_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Chogo in 216?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1178_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Rudolf Duala Manga Bell in the year of 1916?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1179_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Ndumbe Lobe Bell in 1899?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1180_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Stotzas during 547?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1181_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Rasoherina I of Madagascar during 1870?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1182_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Ranavalona II of Madagascar in the year of 1885?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1183_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Rudrama Devi during 1291?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1184_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Margrethe II of Denmark between 1933 and 1938?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1185_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Frederick William von Hessenstein in 1810?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1186_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Otto Magnus von Stackelberg in the year of 1802?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1187_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Florent van Ertborn during 1842?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1188_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Emperor Norton during 1882?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1189_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Emperor Zhenzong of Song during 1024?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1190_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Liu Shan during 273?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1191_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Kharak Singh during 1842?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1192_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Charles I of Bourbon in 1458?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1193_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Raymond Ceulemans between 1996 and 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1194_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of William Alexander Smith during 1916?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1195_ua_en", "question": "What was the noble title of Ashton Lever in 1790?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1196_ua_en", "question": "Rheinische Zeitung was edited by whom in 1845?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1197_ua_en", "question": "Sovremennik was edited by whom in the year of 1868?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1198_ua_en", "question": "Who was the editor of Great Soviet Encyclopedia between 1959 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1199_ua_en", "question": "Who was the editor of Playboy from 1943 to 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1200_ua_en", "question": "Who was the editor of Byzantinische Zeitschrift from 1883 to 1888?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1201_ua_en", "question": "Byzantinische Zeitschrift was edited by whom from 1877 to 1882?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1202_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did Ken Block participate from 1999 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1203_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did John Franklin participate in the year of 1849?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1204_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did Romain Grosjean participate from 1994 to 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1205_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did Felipe Massa participate between 1991 and 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1206_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did George Russell participate between 2005 and 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1207_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did Jens Fiedler participate from 1983 to 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1208_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did Maria Sole Ferrieri Caputi participate between 1994 and 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1209_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did Leo Franco participate between 1993 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1210_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did Abraham Pomerantz participate during 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1211_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did Clarence Campbell participate in 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1212_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did Eberhard Godt participate in 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1213_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did Vladimir Putin participate from 1984 to 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1214_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did Holger Rune participate between 2009 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1215_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did Arthur Rinderknech participate from 2006 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1216_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did George Russell participate between 2006 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1217_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did Eirik Kristoffersen participate from 1983 to 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1218_ua_en", "question": "Which campaign did Maria Sole Ferrieri Caputi participate between 2001 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1219_ua_en", "question": "Who was the commander of XIV Corps during 1921?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1220_ua_en", "question": "Who commanded Mediterranean Division during 1916?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1221_ua_en", "question": "Who was the commander of Admiral Scheer from 1904 to 1909?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1222_ua_en", "question": "Who was the commander of Guards Cavalry Division during 1921?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1223_ua_en", "question": "Who was the commander of Guards Cavalry Division in 1921?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1224_ua_en", "question": "Who was the commander of Admiral Scheer between 1926 and 1931?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1225_ua_en", "question": "Who commanded German battleship Scharnhorst from 1930 to 1935?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1226_ua_en", "question": "Who was the commander of Warsaw Pact in the year of 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1227_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Shell from 1998 to 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1228_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Volkswagen Group from 1938 to 1943?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1229_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of New America from 1984 to 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1230_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Pirelli between 1979 and 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1231_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Robert Bosch between 1995 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1232_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of The Swatch Group between 1967 and 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1233_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of UBS between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1234_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of International Monetary Fund from 1933 to 1938?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1235_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Formula One from 2015 to 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1236_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Westdeutscher Rundfunk between 2006 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1237_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Microsoft between 1958 and 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1238_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Siemens between 1962 and 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1239_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Telegram from 2005 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1240_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Siemens from 1956 to 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1241_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Happy Madison Productions between 1992 and 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1242_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Audi AG between 1993 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1243_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Hilton Worldwide from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1244_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of The Swatch Group from 1977 to 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1245_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Commerzbank AG from 1949 to 1954?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1246_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Porsche between 1945 and 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1247_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Pacific FC from 2003 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1248_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Fidelity Investments between 2006 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1249_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Mistwalker from 1997 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1250_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Heineken between 1962 and 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1251_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of International Monetary Fund between 1930 and 1935?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1252_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Federal Agency on Atomic Energy in 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1253_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Ford Motor Company between 1884 and 1889?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1254_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Shell between 1993 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1255_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of The Walt Disney Company between 1910 and 1915?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1256_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Apple between 1966 and 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1257_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of General Electric from 1974 to 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1258_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Abbott Laboratories from 1990 to 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1259_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of PepsiCo between 1960 and 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1260_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of HM Treasury from 2015 to 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1261_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Amazon from 1981 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1262_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of International Bank for Reconstruction and Development from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1263_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Suzanne Greco from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1264_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Intel from 1942 to 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1265_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of SRI International between 1935 and 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1266_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of HSBC between 1974 and 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1267_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of TotalEnergies between 1916 and 1921?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1268_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of ExxonMobil between 1988 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1269_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of eBay from 1983 to 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1270_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of International Development Association from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1271_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Society of Jesus from 2000 to 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1272_ua_en", "question": "Who was the chief executive officer of Nvidia between 1978 and 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1273_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of PSL University from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1274_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Turner Broadcasting System in the year of 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1275_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Groupe PSA from 1985 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1276_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Stellantis between 2013 and 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1277_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Grupo Globo between 1936 and 1941?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1278_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of University of Lyon between 2004 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1279_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of University of Lyon between 2006 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1280_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Stellantis from 2013 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1281_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of RCA Corporation during 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1282_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Saban Capital Group between 2003 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1283_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Community of universities and higher education institutions of Aquitaine in 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1284_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Community of universities and higher education institutions of Aquitaine in 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1285_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Leonardo da Vinci consolidated University between 2004 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1286_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of United States Department of the Air Force between 1937 and 1942?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1287_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Communist International in 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1288_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Radio France between 1966 and 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1289_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Studebaker during 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1290_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Pershing Square Holdings from 2014 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1291_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of CBS Corporation during 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1292_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of ABB Group from 1979 to 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1293_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Tata Motors Ltd from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1294_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of AMR Corporation in 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1295_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Volkswagen Group from 1957 to 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1296_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Volkswagen Group from 1951 to 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1297_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Cathay Pacific between 1997 and 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1298_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Rockstar Games between 1990 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1299_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Phoenix Group from 2006 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1300_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of eBay from 1990 to 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1301_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Infineon Technologies between 2006 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1302_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Lille North of France University in the year of 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1303_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Kering between 1968 and 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1304_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Liberty Media from 1982 to 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1305_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of McLaren Technology Group between 1955 and 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1306_ua_en", "question": "What was the subsidiary of Simba Dickie Group from 2000 to 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1307_ua_en", "question": "Cyryl Kozaczewski was an ambassador of which Embassy from 2014 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1308_ua_en", "question": "Cyryl Kozaczewski was an ambassador of which Embassy from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1309_ua_en", "question": "Seine was replaced by what in 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1310_ua_en", "question": "Horch was replaced by what in 1942?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1311_ua_en", "question": "Zeevang was replaced by what during 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1312_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Kirnitzschtal in the year of 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1313_ua_en", "question": "Spanish Sahara was replaced by what during 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1314_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Joutseno in 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1315_ua_en", "question": "Seine was replaced by what during 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1316_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Landeszentralbank in 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1317_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Horch in 1942?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1318_ua_en", "question": "Perreuse was replaced by what in 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1319_ua_en", "question": "Entertainment and Leisure Software Publishers Association was replaced by what during 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1320_ua_en", "question": "Waterloo International railway station was replaced by what during 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1321_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Soviet Olympic Committee during 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1322_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Rijksmuseum van Natuurlijke Historie in the year of 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1323_ua_en", "question": "What replaced University of Library and Information Science in 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1324_ua_en", "question": "Bagneux was replaced by what in 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1325_ua_en", "question": "Shirokiya was replaced by what in 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1326_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Eisenhower dollar during 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1327_ua_en", "question": "What replaced Soviet Olympic Committee in the year of 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1328_ua_en", "question": "What was USC Gould School of Law afflicted to between 1892 and 1897?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1329_ua_en", "question": "What was Pedro Szekely afflicted to between 1974 and 1979?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1330_ua_en", "question": "What was Wikimedia France afflicted to from 1999 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1331_ua_en", "question": "What was Tokuro Fujiwara afflicted to from 1973 to 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1332_ua_en", "question": "What was Tokuro Fujiwara afflicted to from 1968 to 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1333_ua_en", "question": "What was Daran Zheng afflicted to between 2001 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1334_ua_en", "question": "What was Qun Zhang afflicted to in 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1335_ua_en", "question": "What was Daran Zheng afflicted to from 1983 to 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1336_ua_en", "question": "What was Gerhard Bigalk afflicted to in the year of 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1337_ua_en", "question": "What was Ethan Vishniac afflicted to from 1966 to 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1338_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of South Prussia in the year of 1809?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1339_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Poland between 1785 and 1790?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1340_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Province of Canada in 1869?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1341_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of South Prussia during 1809?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1342_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Military Administration in Belgium and Northern France during 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1343_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Italy between 1932 and 1937?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1344_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Province of Canada in the year of 1869?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1345_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Habsburg Netherlands in the year of 1583?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1346_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Kingdom of Italy during 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1347_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Grand Duchy of Lithuania in the year of 1797?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1348_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Province of Brandenburg in 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1349_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Switzerland from 1841 to 1846?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1350_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of United States of America between 1766 and 1771?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1351_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Abbasid Caliphate in 1260?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1352_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Egyptian Fatimid Caliphate during 1173?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1353_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Francia during 845?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1354_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of District of Columbia from 1783 to 1788?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1355_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Province of Brandenburg during 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1356_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Germany between 1938 and 1943?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1357_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Germany from 1927 to 1932?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1358_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of United States of America from 1778 to 1783?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1359_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of canton of Poissy between 2006 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1360_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Kingdom of the Burgundians in the year of 536?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1361_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Kalmar Union during 1525?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1362_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Kingdom of Italy in the year of 1948?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1363_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Portugal between 1378 and 1383?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1364_ua_en", "question": "What’s the capital of Italy from 1851 to 1856?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1365_ua_en", "question": "Scoot was operated by what from 2003 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1366_ua_en", "question": "Japan Airlines was operated by what from 1973 to 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1367_ua_en", "question": "Japan Airlines was operated by what from 1975 to 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1368_ua_en", "question": "Swiss Global Air Lines was operated by what in 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1369_ua_en", "question": "All Nippon Airways was operated by what from 1903 to 1908?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1370_ua_en", "question": "Air Italy was operated by what during 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1371_ua_en", "question": "All Nippon Airways was operated by what from 1967 to 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1372_ua_en", "question": "Scoot was operated by what between 1982 and 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1373_ua_en", "question": "Air Italy was operated by what in the year of 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1374_ua_en", "question": "Yemenia was operated by what from 1989 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1375_ua_en", "question": "British Overseas Airways Corporation was operated by what during 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1376_ua_en", "question": "German Air Force was operated by what from 1919 to 1924?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1377_ua_en", "question": "Braathens was operated by what during 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1378_ua_en", "question": "Braathens was operated by what during 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1379_ua_en", "question": "Alyemda was operated by what during 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1380_ua_en", "question": "Meta Platforms was operated by what from 1998 to 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1381_ua_en", "question": "Kalstar Aviation was operated by what in the year of 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1382_ua_en", "question": "Japan Air Commuter was operated by what between 1979 and 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1383_ua_en", "question": "Japan Air Commuter was operated by what between 1984 and 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1384_ua_en", "question": "Hokkaido Air System was operated by what from 1986 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1385_ua_en", "question": "East Japan Railway Company was operated by what from 1972 to 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1386_ua_en", "question": "British Overseas Airways Corporation was operated by what in 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1387_ua_en", "question": "Germania was operated by what in the year of 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1388_ua_en", "question": "East Japan Railway Company was operated by what from 1977 to 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1389_ua_en", "question": "Austrian Airlines was operated by what between 1956 and 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1390_ua_en", "question": "Jim Watkins was operated by what from 2004 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1391_ua_en", "question": "German Air Force was operated by what from 1944 to 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1392_ua_en", "question": "Central Japan Railway Company was operated by what from 1980 to 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1393_ua_en", "question": "Swiss International Air Lines was operated by what from 1992 to 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1394_ua_en", "question": "Finnair was operated by what between 1917 and 1922?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1395_ua_en", "question": "Cornell University Library was operated by what between 1991 and 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1396_ua_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Rostec between 2010 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1397_ua_en", "question": "Who owned Seoul Metropolitan Government between 1973 and 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1398_ua_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Josh Harris from 1983 to 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1399_ua_en", "question": "Who owned Mike Ashley from 1993 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1400_ua_en", "question": "Who owned Westinghouse Electric Corporation during 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1401_ua_en", "question": "Who owned Ronald Wayne between 1970 and 1975?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1402_ua_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Bernard Tapie between 1965 and 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1403_ua_en", "question": "Who owned Elon Musk between 2013 and 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1404_ua_en", "question": "Who owned Josh Harris from 2001 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1405_ua_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Bernard Tapie between 1961 and 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1406_ua_en", "question": "Who owned LVMH between 1939 and 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1407_ua_en", "question": "Who owned General Electric from 1978 to 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1408_ua_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Michael Kors between 2005 and 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1409_ua_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Otto von Bismarck in 1900?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1410_ua_en", "question": "Who owned CoStar Group between 1960 and 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1411_ua_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Ford Motor Company from 1910 to 1915?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1412_ua_en", "question": "Who was the owner of United Artists Corporation in 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1413_ua_en", "question": "Who was the owner of Exor between 2003 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1414_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Spain from 1923 to 1928?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1415_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Civitas Schinesghe during 1027?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1416_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Saint Lucia from 1968 to 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1417_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Poland between 1982 and 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1418_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Indonesia between 1933 and 1938?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1419_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Poland from 1976 to 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1420_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of South Korea between 1942 and 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1421_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Georgia between 1978 and 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1422_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Turkey between 1907 and 1912?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1423_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Ghana between 2005 and 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1424_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of New Zealand between 1929 and 1934?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1425_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Tuvalu between 1958 and 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1426_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Jersey between 2014 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1427_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Brazil from 1950 to 1955?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1428_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Syria from 1991 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1429_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Georgia from 1968 to 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1430_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Romania between 1833 and 1838?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1431_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Solomon Islands from 2011 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1432_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Saint Vincent and the Grenadines from 2015 to 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1433_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Saint Kitts and Nevis from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1434_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Papua New Guinea from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1435_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Antigua and Barbuda between 2011 and 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1436_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Nova Scotia from 2015 to 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1437_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of North Korea from 1939 to 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1438_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Sweden between 1811 and 1816?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1439_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of India between 1906 and 1911?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1440_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Croatia from 1973 to 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1441_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Sweden from 1793 to 1798?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1442_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Turkey from 1901 to 1906?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1443_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Jamaica from 2012 to 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1444_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of The Bahamas from 2008 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1445_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Mataram Sultanate in the year of 1757?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1446_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Belize between 2015 and 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1447_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Australia between 1941 and 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1448_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Saskatchewan between 2007 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1449_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Grenada from 2009 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1450_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Gibraltar from 1945 to 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1451_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Civitas Schinesghe during 1027?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1452_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Romania from 1855 to 1860?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1453_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Isle of Man from 2008 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1454_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Falkland Islands between 2014 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1455_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of England from 2014 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1456_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Vatican City between 1919 and 1924?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1457_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Bailiwick of Guernsey from 2014 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1458_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Soviet Union during 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1459_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of East Francia during 964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1460_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Cook Islands between 1934 and 1939?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1461_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Iran between 1966 and 1971?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1462_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Bulgaria from 1967 to 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1463_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of North Korea from 1933 to 1938?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1464_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Niue between 2010 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1465_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Alberta from 1894 to 1899?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1466_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Cuba between 1996 and 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1467_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Weimar Republic in 1935?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1468_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Germany between 1941 and 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1469_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Philippines from 1923 to 1928?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1470_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Italy between 1932 and 1937?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1471_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Germany from 1936 to 1941?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1472_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Austria between 1906 and 1911?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1473_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of France from 1940 to 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1474_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Chile between 1968 and 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1475_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Philippines from 1928 to 1933?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1476_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Military dictatorship of Chile during 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1477_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of France between 1916 and 1921?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1478_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Chile between 1984 and 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1479_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Kingdom of Bosnia in 1465?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1480_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Vatican City from 1912 to 1917?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1481_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Italy from 1929 to 1934?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1482_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of Mongol Empire in 1370?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1483_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of German Empire in the year of 1920?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1484_ua_en", "question": "Who was the president of First French Empire in the year of 1816?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1485_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Qt Group from 2001 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1486_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Bell Labs from 1904 to 1909?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1487_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned Jeppesen between 1986 and 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1488_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned Rocketdyne during 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1489_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned DoubleClick from 1999 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1490_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned Fitbit from 2009 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1491_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Google DeepMind between 2003 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1492_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned Motorola Mobility from 2001 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1493_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Niantic from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1494_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of MD Helicopters between 1957 and 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1495_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Boston Dynamics from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1496_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned Mobileye between 2004 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1497_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Reality Labs from 2000 to 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1498_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned Wind River Systems from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1499_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Mapillary AB from 2012 to 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1500_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Gamepedia between 2009 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1501_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Danger Close Games during 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1502_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned Jean Monnet University between 1989 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1503_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned German Labor Front during 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1504_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Sikorsky Aircraft Corporation from 1876 to 1881?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1505_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Tazo between 1989 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1506_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned Mills College at Northeastern from 2009 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1507_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Dehomag during 1951?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1508_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of DreamWorks Records in the year of 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1509_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned Red Hat from 2009 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1510_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned Okinawa General Bureau between 1959 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1511_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Dacia between 1990 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1512_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned Berliet during 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1513_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Imperial Household Agency between 1942 and 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1514_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Glidden between 2007 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1515_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Monte Carlo Doualiya between 1954 and 1959?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1516_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Harman International Industries between 2010 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1517_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned Transportation Security Administration from 1993 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1518_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned United States Hydrographic Office during 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1519_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned Federal Law Enforcement Training Center from 1953 to 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1520_ua_en", "question": "Which organization owned Bungie from 2014 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1521_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of FC Cincinnati from 2009 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1522_ua_en", "question": "What was the parent organization of Indiana Bell between 1906 and 1911?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1523_ua_en", "question": "What was Design Museum used for from 1889 to 1894?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1524_ua_en", "question": "What was Hospital train used for between 1906 and 1911?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1525_ua_en", "question": "What was Rimnersvallen used for from 1946 to 1951?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1526_ua_en", "question": "Which league did AFC Bournemouth play for between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1527_ua_en", "question": "Which league did AFC Bournemouth play for between 2006 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1528_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Vincent Kompany play for from 1982 to 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1529_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Jonatan Johansson play for from 1988 to 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1530_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Romelu Lukaku play for from 1987 to 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1531_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Romelu Lukaku play for from 1996 to 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1532_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Gareth Bale play for between 2000 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1533_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Erik Lamela play for between 2000 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1534_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Leon Bailey play for from 2006 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1535_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Christian Pulisic play for from 2008 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1536_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Spezia Calcio play for from 1996 to 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1537_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Juventus FC play for between 1918 and 1923?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1538_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Inter Milan play for between 1923 and 1928?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1539_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Udinese Calcio play for from 1983 to 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1540_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Atalanta BC play for from 1997 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1541_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Cagliari Calcio play for between 2002 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1542_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Torino Football Club play for from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1543_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Juventus FC play for between 1918 and 1923?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1544_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Dor Peretz play for from 1990 to 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1545_ua_en", "question": "Which league did ACF Fiorentina play for between 1989 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1546_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Genoa CFC play for from 1995 to 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1547_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Brescia Calcio play for from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1548_ua_en", "question": "Which league did AC Milan play for from 1968 to 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1549_ua_en", "question": "Which league did AC Monza play for between 2014 and 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1550_ua_en", "question": "Which league did David Beckham play for between 1997 and 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1551_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Jeff Agoos play for from 1981 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1552_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Celtic Warriors play for during 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1553_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Oyonnax Rugby play for from 1991 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1554_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Oyonnax Rugby play for between 1995 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1555_ua_en", "question": "Which league did ASM Clermont Auvergne play for from 1917 to 1922?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1556_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Cobi Jones play for between 1978 and 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1557_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Philadelphia Union play for between 1998 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1558_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Cobi Jones play for between 1984 and 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1559_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Cagliari Calcio play for between 2010 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1560_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Benevento Calcio play for between 2006 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1561_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Tajon Buchanan play for between 2012 and 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1562_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Erik Lamela play for from 1999 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1563_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Cristiano Ronaldo play for between 1976 and 1981?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1564_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Elif Elmas play for from 2009 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1565_ua_en", "question": "Which league did Genoa CFC play for between 1997 and 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1566_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Olympique Lyonnais between 1944 and 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1567_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of France national association football team between 1990 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1568_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Heracles Almelo from 1892 to 1897?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1569_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of France national rugby union team between 1876 and 1881?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1570_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Olympique Lyonnais from 1916 to 1921?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1571_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Cagliari Calcio between 1898 and 1903?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1572_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of AFC Wimbledon between 1986 and 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1573_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Jokerit between 1989 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1574_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Ermis Aradippou FC from 1951 to 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1575_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Nea Salamis Famagusta FC from 1945 to 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1576_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Nea Salamis Famagusta FC from 1932 to 1937?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1577_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Anorthosis Famagusta FC from 1922 to 1927?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1578_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Golden State Warriors from 1935 to 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1579_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Washington Mystics between 1983 and 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1580_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of FC Girondins de Bordeaux between 1922 and 1927?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1581_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Washington Wizards between 1954 and 1959?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1582_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of ADO Den Haag from 1912 to 1917?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1583_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Los Angeles Rams between 1936 and 1941?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1584_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Vancouver Canucks from 1927 to 1932?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1585_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Vancouver Grizzlies in 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1586_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Washington Nationals from 1951 to 1956?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1587_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Montreal Canadiens between 1874 and 1879?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1588_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Catalans Dragons between 2000 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1589_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Minnesota Timberwolves from 1975 to 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1590_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Sporting CP from 1940 to 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1591_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Washington Nationals between 1941 and 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1592_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Montreal Expos between 1927 and 1932?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1593_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of RCD Mallorca from 1929 to 1934?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1594_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of FC Porto from 1941 to 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1595_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Barcelona Dragons during 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1596_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Kansas City Chiefs from 1952 to 1957?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1597_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Sporting Kansas City from 1989 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1598_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Indiana Fever between 1993 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1599_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Indiana Pacers between 1956 and 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1600_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Indiana Fever between 1979 and 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1601_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Portland Trail Blazers between 1959 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1602_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Los Angeles Lakers between 1931 and 1936?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1603_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Chicago Bulls between 1952 and 1957?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1604_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Chicago Blackhawks between 1922 and 1927?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1605_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Chicago White Sox from 1980 to 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1606_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Valencia CF from 1915 to 1920?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1607_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Juventus FC from 1977 to 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1608_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of AFC Ajax between 1901 and 1906?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1609_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Detroit Pistons between 1920 and 1925?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1610_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Juventus FC between 1964 and 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1611_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of FC Bayern Munich from 1940 to 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1612_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Catalans Dragons from 1989 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1613_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Edmonton Elks from 1930 to 1935?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1614_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Israel national football team between 1950 and 1955?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1615_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of FC Bayern Munich between 1959 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1616_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Erie SeaWolves from 1984 to 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1617_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Orix Buffaloes from 1917 to 1922?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1618_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Real Madrid Baloncesto between 1942 and 1947?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1619_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Brooklyn Nets between 1945 and 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1620_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Real Madrid Baloncesto from 1950 to 1955?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1621_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of San Antonio Spurs from 1947 to 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1622_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of AZ Alkmaar from 1935 to 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1623_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Chiba Lotte Marines between 1921 and 1926?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1624_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Orlando Magic between 1978 and 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1625_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Orlando Magic from 1981 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1626_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Roda JC Kerkrade between 1988 and 1993?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1627_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of France national rugby union team from 1899 to 1904?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1628_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of San Diego State Aztecs football from 1913 to 1918?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1629_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Los Angeles Chargers between 1952 and 1957?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1630_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Golden State Warriors between 1897 and 1902?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1631_ua_en", "question": "What was the home venue of Memphis Grizzlies between 1994 and 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1632_ua_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Sovremennik during 1868?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1633_ua_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Crash Bandicoot from 1986 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1634_ua_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Neues Deutschland from 1938 to 1943?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1635_ua_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Byzantinische Zeitschrift between 1883 and 1888?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1636_ua_en", "question": "What was the publisher of IEEE Annals of the History of Computing between 1980 and 1985?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1637_ua_en", "question": "What was the publisher of New York World during 1933?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1638_ua_en", "question": "What was the publisher of IBM Journal of Research and Development in the year of 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1639_ua_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Zork from 1955 to 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1640_ua_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Tumor Biology between 1998 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1641_ua_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Virtual International Authority File between 2003 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1642_ua_en", "question": "What was the publisher of Crash Bandicoot from 1984 to 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1643_ua_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of SimCity from 1891 to 1896?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1644_ua_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of SimCity between 1880 and 1885?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1645_ua_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of The Tin Drum from 1932 to 1937?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1646_ua_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of Khovanshchina from 1674 to 1679?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1647_ua_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of Anne of the Island from 1872 to 1877?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1648_ua_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of Anne of Green Gables from 1965 to 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1649_ua_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of Anne of the Island from 1877 to 1882?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1650_ua_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of Naked Among Wolves from 1939 to 1944?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1651_ua_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of Robinson Crusoe between 1642 and 1647?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1652_ua_en", "question": "What was the narrative location of The Tin Drum between 1935 and 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1653_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did Wendell Ford belong to in the year of 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1654_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Alvin York in the year of 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1655_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Hal Moore in 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1656_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did Colonel Sanders belong to in 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1657_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Douglas MacArthur in 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1658_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Frank Lautenberg during 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1659_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did Norman Mineta belong to between 1941 and 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1660_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of David Glantz from 1950 to 1955?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1661_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Ted Kennedy during 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1662_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did Theodore Roosevelt belong to in the year of 1921?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1663_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Nipsey Russell in the year of 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1664_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did Rodney Frelinghuysen belong to between 1962 and 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1665_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did Greg Steube belong to from 1990 to 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1666_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Robert Duvall from 1944 to 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1667_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of James Joseph Dresnok in 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1668_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Ronald Reagan during 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1669_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did Adam Clymer belong to in the year of 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1670_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did William Roth belong to in the year of 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1671_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did Rob Simmons belong to from 1957 to 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1672_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did John Conyers belong to in the year of 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1673_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did Wint Smith belong to during 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1674_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Doug Bereuter from 1952 to 1957?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1675_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did Henry Wharton Conway belong to in the year of 1829?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1676_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did Wint Smith belong to during 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1677_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Tim Conway in the year of 2021?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1678_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did Allen West belong to from 1973 to 1978?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1679_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Emanuel Celler in 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1680_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did Malcolm Forbes belong to in 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1681_ua_en", "question": "Which military brach did Joe Medicine Crow belong to in the year of 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1682_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Ty Carter between 1968 and 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1683_ua_en", "question": "What was the military branch of Truman Smith during 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1684_ua_en", "question": "Who was the rector of Humboldt University of Berlin between 1984 and 1989?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1685_ua_en", "question": "Who was the rector of Heidelberg University between 1912 and 1917?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1686_ua_en", "question": "Who was the rector of Heidelberg University between 1891 and 1896?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1687_ua_en", "question": "What was Hans Beimler engaged or conflicted with during 1938?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1688_ua_en", "question": "What was Constantin Cristescu engaged or conflicted with in the year of 1925?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1689_ua_en", "question": "What was Constantin Prezan engaged or conflicted with in the year of 1945?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1690_ua_en", "question": "What was Karl Gebhardt engaged or conflicted with during 1950?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1691_ua_en", "question": "What was Aristide Razu engaged or conflicted with in the year of 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1692_ua_en", "question": "What was Wilhelm Leuschner engaged or conflicted with in the year of 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1693_ua_en", "question": "What was the terminus of Vindobona during 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1694_ua_en", "question": "What was the terminus of Istanbul Express between 1979 and 1984?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1695_ua_en", "question": "What was the terminus of Capitol Limited during 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1696_ua_en", "question": "What was the terminus of Vindobona in 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1697_ua_en", "question": "What was the terminus of Seibu Shinjuku Line between 1885 and 1890?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1698_ua_en", "question": "What was the terminus of Seoul Metropolitan Subway Seohae Line between 2012 and 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1699_ua_en", "question": "What was the terminus of Nasuno from 1983 to 1988?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1700_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The Little Lulu Show between 1991 and 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1701_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of YOUniverse from 2008 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1702_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of YOUniverse from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1703_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Go On Girl Star Search between 2009 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1704_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Go On Girl Star Search between 2003 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1705_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of BlackBoxTV Presents between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1706_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Parenthood from 1996 to 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1707_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Knight Rider between 1971 and 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1708_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of ALF from 1972 to 1977?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1709_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Fame between 1967 and 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1710_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Scrubs between 1989 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1711_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Medical Investigation between 1994 and 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1712_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of National Geographic Explorer between 1987 and 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1713_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Imus in the Morning from 1986 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1714_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Las Vegas between 1994 and 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1715_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Alfred Hitchcock Presents between 1948 and 1953?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1716_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Alfred Hitchcock Presents between 1926 and 1931?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1717_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Medium between 1996 and 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1718_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Holocaust between 1968 and 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1719_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The Office between 1998 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1720_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Deal or No Deal from 1993 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1721_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Blindspot from 2001 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1722_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The Player between 2005 and 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1723_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Best Time Ever with Neil Patrick Harris between 2000 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1724_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Late Night with Seth Meyers between 2001 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1725_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Truth Be Told from 2006 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1726_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Heroes Reborn between 2002 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1727_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of JAG from 1981 to 1986?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1728_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The Phantom of the Opera between 1975 and 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1729_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Constantine between 2000 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1730_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon from 2008 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1731_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Silver Spoons between 1971 and 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1732_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Knight Rider between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1733_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Hazel from 1948 to 1953?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1734_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Taxi from 1952 to 1957?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1735_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Friday Night Lights between 1997 and 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1736_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Little House on the Prairie from 1961 to 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1737_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The High Chaparral between 1959 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1738_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Late Night with Jimmy Fallon from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1739_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Marco Polo between 1969 and 1974?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1740_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of In the Heat of the Night between 1975 and 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1741_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The West Wing from 1987 to 1992?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1742_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Santa Barbara between 1978 and 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1743_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Meet the Press between 1937 and 1942?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1744_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Saved by the Bell between 1982 and 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1745_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Saturday Night Live from 1960 to 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1746_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Ed from 1986 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1747_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of V from 1970 to 1975?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1748_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of The Apprentice between 1989 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1749_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of American Odyssey from 2004 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1750_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Hardball with Chris Matthews from 1985 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1751_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Morning Joe from 1999 to 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1752_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of All My Children between 2007 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1753_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Countdown with Keith Olbermann between 1991 and 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1754_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Countdown with Keith Olbermann between 1970 and 1975?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1755_ua_en", "question": "Who was the original broadcaster of Aquarius from 2001 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1756_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Panther Chan from 2009 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1757_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Chris Martin from 1991 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1758_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Alan Stivell between 1947 and 1952?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1759_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Mon Laferte between 1990 and 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1760_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Rip Slyme between 1965 and 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1761_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Three Days Grace between 1994 and 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1762_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Mike Oldfield between 1955 and 1960?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1763_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Shiga Lin between 1995 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1764_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Alec Benjamin from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1765_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of David Guetta from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1766_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Lady Gaga between 1998 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1767_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Chris Martin from 1970 to 1975?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1768_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Miki Imai from 1958 to 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1769_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Lady Gaga from 1993 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1770_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of SG Lewis from 2006 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1771_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Kaija Koo from 1967 to 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1772_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Passpo between 2000 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1773_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Olavi Uusivirta between 1995 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1774_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Martin Garrix from 1985 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1775_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Cecilia Cheung from 1990 to 1995?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1776_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Loreen between 1992 and 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1777_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Kei between 2003 and 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1778_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Ismael Serrano from 1986 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1779_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Nina Nesbitt between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1780_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Mon Laferte between 1996 and 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1781_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Lee Jaijin between 2001 and 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1782_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of CL from 2002 to 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1783_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Mura Masa from 2008 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1784_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Lee Hi from 2003 to 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1785_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Annie Cordy in 2022?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1786_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of John Cale between 1964 and 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1787_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Selena Gomez between 1995 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1788_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Sechs Kies between 2002 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1789_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of One between 2008 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1790_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Hilary Duff from 1995 to 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1791_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Jang Su Won between 2005 and 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1792_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Kim Jaeduck between 2007 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1793_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Kang Sung Hun between 2007 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1794_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of MC Solaar from 1977 to 1982?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1795_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Borknagar between 1989 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1796_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Mura Masa from 2000 to 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1797_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Bee Gees between 1932 and 1937?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1798_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Dadju from 1991 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1799_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Omnium Gatherum from 2001 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1800_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Insomnium between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1801_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Madonna between 1971 and 1976?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1802_ua_en", "question": "What was the record label of Maurizio Pollini between 1962 and 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1803_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did Stardew Valley use from 2004 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1804_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did The Room use from 2005 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1805_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did Stardew Valley use from 2008 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1806_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did Touhou Project use from 1967 to 1972?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1807_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did Dead Cells use from 2006 to 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1808_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did Bad North use between 2009 and 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1809_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did Pingus use from 2001 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1810_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did Pingus use from 1996 to 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1811_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did The Room use from 1997 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1812_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did Discord use from 2015 to 2020?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1813_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did Touhou Project use from 1989 to 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1814_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did Potlatch use between 2012 and 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1815_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did Jurassic World Evolution use from 2014 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1816_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did Factorio use from 2013 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1817_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did Shadowverse use from 2011 to 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1818_ua_en", "question": "Which platform did MicroPython use from 2008 to 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1819_ua_en", "question": "Which child of Hemma was born in the year of 878?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1820_ua_en", "question": "Which child of Hemma was born during 878?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1821_ua_en", "question": "Which child of Miyamoto Musashi was born in 1647?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1822_ua_en", "question": "Which child of Henry Fok was born in 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1823_ua_en", "question": "Which child of Henry Fok was born in the year of 2008?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1824_ua_en", "question": "Which child of Run Run Shaw was born during 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1825_ua_en", "question": "Albrecht Brandi was a crew member of what in the year of 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1826_ua_en", "question": "Which crew did Engelbert Endrass belong to during 1943?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1827_ua_en", "question": "Engelbert Endrass was a crew member of what in the year of 1943?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1828_ua_en", "question": "Which crew did Albrecht Brandi belong to in 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1829_ua_en", "question": "Victor Oehrn was a crew member of what in the year of 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1830_ua_en", "question": "Victor Oehrn was a crew member of what in 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1831_ua_en", "question": "Felix von Bendemann was a crew member of what in 1917?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1832_ua_en", "question": "Heinrich Liebe was a crew member of what during 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1833_ua_en", "question": "Albert Lauzemis was a crew member of what during 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1834_ua_en", "question": "Sian Proctor was a crew member of what between 2007 and 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1835_ua_en", "question": "What was the family name of Camille Grammer from 1982 to 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1836_ua_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Viktor Ullmann in the year of 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1837_ua_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Al Capone in the year of 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1838_ua_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Al Capone in 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1839_ua_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Donald Tsang from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1840_ua_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Albert Speer in the year of 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1841_ua_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Tommy Chong between 1993 and 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1842_ua_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Jefferson Davis in the year of 1891?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1843_ua_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Sergei Magnitsky in 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1844_ua_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Viktor Frankl in 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1845_ua_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Hubert Robert in 1810?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1846_ua_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Hubert Robert in the year of 1810?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1847_ua_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Shyne from 1991 to 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1848_ua_en", "question": "What was the place of detention for Naftaly Frenkel during 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1849_ua_en", "question": "Where was Idol charted in from 2013 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1850_ua_en", "question": "Where was Machine Head charted in from 1960 to 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1851_ua_en", "question": "Where was Machine Head charted in from 1957 to 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1852_ua_en", "question": "Where was Jesus Christ Superstar charted in from 1964 to 1969?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1853_ua_en", "question": "Where was Imagine charted in from 1961 to 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1854_ua_en", "question": "Where was Jesus Christ Superstar charted in from 1961 to 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1855_ua_en", "question": "Where was Shaft charted in between 1961 and 1966?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1856_ua_en", "question": "Where was All Things Must Pass charted in from 1958 to 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1857_ua_en", "question": "Where was No Time to Die charted in from 2007 to 2012?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1858_ua_en", "question": "Where was Tapestry charted in between 1965 and 1970?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1859_ua_en", "question": "Where was We Found Love charted in from 1997 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1860_ua_en", "question": "Where was American Pie charted in from 1958 to 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1861_ua_en", "question": "Where was Old Town Road charted in between 2008 and 2013?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1862_ua_en", "question": "Where was One More Night charted in from 2005 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1863_ua_en", "question": "Where was Set Fire to the Rain charted in from 1998 to 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1864_ua_en", "question": "Where was Sunflower charted in from 2010 to 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1865_ua_en", "question": "Where was Diamonds charted in between 1997 and 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1866_ua_en", "question": "Where was Shallow charted in between 2011 and 2016?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1867_ua_en", "question": "Where was We Are Young charted in from 2001 to 2006?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1868_ua_en", "question": "Where was Somebody That I Used to Know charted in from 1997 to 2002?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1869_ua_en", "question": "Where was Locked Out of Heaven charted in between 1999 and 2004?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1870_ua_en", "question": "Where was Whistle charted in from 2004 to 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1871_ua_en", "question": "Where was No Time to Die charted in from 2014 to 2019?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1872_ua_en", "question": "Where was Truth Hurts charted in from 2013 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1873_ua_en", "question": "Where was Lose You to Love Me charted in from 2013 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1874_ua_en", "question": "Where was We Are Never Ever Getting Back Together charted in from 2005 to 2010?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1875_ua_en", "question": "Where was Sucker charted in from 2013 to 2018?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1876_ua_en", "question": "Where was Ram charted in from 1962 to 1967?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1877_ua_en", "question": "Where was Bridge over Troubled Water charted in from 1960 to 1965?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1878_ua_en", "question": "Where was Bridge over Troubled Water charted in from 1957 to 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1879_ua_en", "question": "Where was Imagine charted in from 1957 to 1962?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1880_ua_en", "question": "Where was All Things Must Pass charted in between 1959 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1881_ua_en", "question": "Where was Led Zeppelin IV charted in between 1956 and 1961?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1882_ua_en", "question": "Who participated in World Curling Federation during 1955?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1883_ua_en", "question": "Who participated in International Organization of Journalists in 1932?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1884_ua_en", "question": "Who participated in World Curling Federation in the year of 1946?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1885_ua_en", "question": "Who participated in International Convention on Load Lines during 1959?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1886_ua_en", "question": "Who participated in International Organization of Journalists in the year of 1940?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1887_ua_en", "question": "Who participated in National Popular Vote Interstate Compact during 1999?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1888_ua_en", "question": "Who participated in National Popular Vote Interstate Compact in 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1889_ua_en", "question": "What was the country of registry for Gauss from 1897 to 1902?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1890_ua_en", "question": "What was the country of registry for HMCS Bonaventure between 1918 and 1923?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1891_ua_en", "question": "What was the country of registry for HSC Natchan Rera between 2000 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1892_ua_en", "question": "What was the country of registry for ADV Ocean Shield between 1970 and 1975?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1893_ua_en", "question": "United States Marine Forces Europe and Africa applied to which place between 1998 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1894_ua_en", "question": "Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement applied to which place between 2002 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1895_ua_en", "question": "Mint applied to which place between 1998 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1896_ua_en", "question": "Regional Comprehensive Economic Partnership applied to which place from 2009 to 2014?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1897_ua_en", "question": "Protocol against the Illicit Manufacturing of and Trafficking in Firearms applied to which place between 2002 and 2007?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1898_ua_en", "question": "limited liability partnership applied to which place from 1975 to 1980?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1899_ua_en", "question": "Forestry Commission applied to which place between 1910 and 1915?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1900_ua_en", "question": "Forestry Commission applied to which place between 1912 and 1917?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1901_ua_en", "question": "Hymn of Riego applied to which place from 1809 to 1814?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1902_ua_en", "question": "limited liability partnership applied to which place from 1978 to 1983?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1903_ua_en", "question": "Miranda warning applied to which place from 1954 to 1959?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1904_ua_en", "question": "Senate of Finland applied to which place in the year of 1920?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1905_ua_en", "question": "Prespa agreement applied to which place between 2004 and 2009?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1906_ua_en", "question": "Protocol III applied to which place between 1998 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1907_ua_en", "question": "French university master applied to which place between 1952 and 1957?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1908_ua_en", "question": "Charter of the Forest applied to which place between 1784 and 1789?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1909_ua_en", "question": "Parliament of the United Kingdom applied to which place between 1782 and 1787?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1910_ua_en", "question": "Act of the Parliament of the United Kingdom applied to which place between 1784 and 1789?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1911_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Deborah Levi participate between 2000 and 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1912_ua_en", "question": "What sport did World Athletics participate between 1898 and 1903?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1913_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Carlyle Eubank participate between 1995 and 2000?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1914_ua_en", "question": "What sport did FC Winterthur participate between 1910 and 1915?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1915_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Adriano Panatta participate between 1959 and 1964?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1916_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Ashleigh Barty participate between 2006 and 2011?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1917_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Tennis Borussia Berlin participate from 1887 to 1892?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1918_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Hard Rock Stadium participate between 1944 and 1949?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1919_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Ellis Park Stadium participate from 1923 to 1928?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1920_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Rio Haryanto participate between 1989 and 1994?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1921_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Nello Pagani participate in the year of 2005?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1922_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Fittipaldi Automotive participate between 1963 and 1968?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1923_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Paul di Resta participate from 1993 to 1998?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1924_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Charles Leclerc participate from 1982 to 1987?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1925_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Sebastian Vettel participate from 1996 to 2001?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1926_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Fittipaldi FD participate between 1968 and 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1927_ua_en", "question": "What sport did All American Racers participate from 1953 to 1958?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1928_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Alex Zanardi participate from 1985 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1929_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Marcus Ericsson participate from 1985 to 1990?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1930_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Surtees participate from 1958 to 1963?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1931_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Esteban Ocon participate between 2010 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1932_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Stoffel Vandoorne participate from 1986 to 1991?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1933_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Geoff Duke participate in 2017?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1934_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Brendon Hartley participate between 2010 and 2015?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1935_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Max Verstappen participate from 1968 to 1973?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1936_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Pascal Wehrlein participate between 1992 and 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1937_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Jolyon Palmer participate between 1991 and 1996?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1938_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Keepmoat Stadium participate between 1998 and 2003?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1939_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Jarry Park Stadium participate in the year of 1997?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}, {"qid": "time_1940_ua_en", "question": "What sport did Estadio GEBA participate between 1900 and 1905?", "answer": [{"label": "None", "id": "None"}], "type": "unanswerable", "cls_target": "No", "lan": "en"}]